(Sanjicheon on Jeju Island with the blue sea and blue sky)
(There's Sanjitmul Park next to Sanjicheon.)
My gosh.
哎喲喂
(The members are gathering at the park.)
Hello, guys.
大家都好嗎
Seok Sam.
石三啊
(Seok Sam follows as he grumbles.)
- Excuse me. - Seok Sam.
那位先生
- Excuse me. - Come here, Seok Sam.
石三啊
-那位 -快過來石三
(What's this skit?)
You haven't taught me anything for the past 15 years.
現在
-現在什麼都沒教過我 -石三
(Human Cultural Asset Jae Seok, and his pupil, Seok Sam)
(Immersed)
- Do you want me to leave? - Stay quiet, Seok Sam.
-我走了哦直接 -安靜點 石三
- This is just... - Don't talk too much.
不是
你別說太多話
(Seok Sam's stopped from talking for 15 years.)
You just let me do the laundry.
每天就讓我洗衣服
So you're Seok Sam.
-石三很委屈啊 -我家石三
(And these two are...)
- He's Jee Seok Sam. - Hello.
(Assistant Manager Haha, new recruit Jong Kook)
你好
Hello.
-你好你好 -你好
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo say hi politely.)
- Hello. - Hello.
你好你好
(Math Olympiad winner Ji Hyo, Math Olympiad runner-up Kwang Soo)
Nice to meet you.
-大家好 -你好 你好你好
(Se Chan and So Min are wearing matching outfits.)
- Hello. - Hello.
Nice to meet you.
是 大家好
(A newlywed couple, Se Chan and So Min)
Nice to meet you. I guess you are married.
你好 看來結婚了啊
(Nosy)
- Right. - We've been married for a year.
是的
結婚第一年
(The skit experts have gathered.)
So you're on a trip to Jeju Island.
But the husband...
這位丈夫
Is the husband rich?
這位丈夫是富人嗎
Is he rich?
What's that supposed to mean?
你什麼意思
He's a rich man with a lot of teeth.
牙齦富人牙齦富人
(Se Chan is always rich in a couple skit.)
I do have many teeth.
我是牙齦富人
- So... - What did you do for a living?
您以前是幹什麼
- I ran my own business. - What business?
-我從商什麼的 -都幹什麼呢
I used to handle big money.
我摸過大錢的
What did you do?
你說什麼 啥
He runs a restaurant.
-開餐館 餐館 -餐館嗎
- A restaurant? - Spicy catfish stew.
辣味鮎魚湯
(Mr. Yang sells fish that look like him.)
- Spicy catfish stew. - A restaurant.
啊辣味鮎魚湯
- Do you live in Paju? - Yes. How did you know?
做的韓餐這方面的嘛
(He sells catfish and Korean bullhead.)
He sells spicy catfish and Korean bullhead stew.
做得鮎魚 辣味鮎魚湯
(This couple owns a big restaurant.)
- It tastes really good. - You should visit my restaurant.
可好吃了
隨時過來玩
(The husband made a lot of money from selling freshwater fish.)
I'll offer a discount of 15 percent.
大家得來喫一下新婚宴
(What brings the newlywed couple to Jeju Island?)
So what brings you two here?
新婚夫妻來這兒多久了
I said I didn't want to come to Jeju Island.
我都說了我不喜歡來濟州島
Don't raise your voice when there are people around.
在人多的地方又在說些什麼大話
- Honey... - My goodness.
-也太也太 -真是的 又
- I mean... - Don't embarrass me.
-不是 -你饒了我吧
I'm sorry, but who picked out your sunglasses?
但是不好意思 兩位的墨鏡到底是誰選的
Why? Aren't they nice? I picked them.
怎麼了
很有眼光吧
(He picked cyborg sunglasses.)
我選的
- You look pretty. - Honey.
很漂亮嗯
You look great.
也太
很漂亮
(The husband loves his wife.)
- You two... - You're so pretty.
-兩位 -漂亮漂亮
Don't make fun of her. She looks pretty.
-工作努力啊 -不要嘲笑我們 明明這麼好看
(Out of nowhere)
Why did you marry him?
-到底是喜歡那一點決定結婚的 -那個 石三啊
- Seok Sam. - Yes?
- Don't be nosy. - What? Hey.
-怎麼了 -不要搞人物設定
(The human cultural asset stops Seok Sam from being nosy.)
I like their skit.
人物設定把握得很好
Seok Sam is too nosy.
-石三人設也太明顯了 -喂
(Complaining)
- I'm sorry. - You should talk to him.
-不是 -認真點吧
Sir, I just said 1 word while you said 5.
文化遺產先生 在家裏說五句話 我就說了一句
Seok Sam, just stay quiet.
石三啊
- Seok Sam. - Watch your language.
不要口不擇言
- Is his name Seok Sam? - Yes.
-名字叫石三先生嗎 -是的是的
(Is the student's name Seok Sam?)
- Like how you count numbers. - I see.
一崽，兩崽子，石三，四古力
(Korean style naming)
- Seok Sam means three. - That's what it means.
-所以他是石三 -原來是這樣啊
I've never seen him paint.
但是我從來沒看到過這個人畫畫
(Conspiracy theory)
- I've never seen his work. - I do an ink-and-wash painting.
我是畫水墨畫的 水墨畫
(He's an ink-and-wash painting human cultural asset.)
- An ink painting. - I just saw him draw a mustache.
-剛纔自己畫了鬍子 -就是說啊
Sure. It's a kind of ink painting.
這也是畫水墨畫的人才能畫出來的
(He drew a painting on top of his protruding mouth.)
- He does draw pictures. - Sure.
-這就是畫的畫 -那可不
(Title: Petty)
- Are you sure? - Don't worry.
別擔心了
Are you Math Olympiad winners? It sounds far-fetched.
但是奧林匹克學科競賽獲勝者的設定
(1st place, 2nd place)
- I was a runner-up. - I was the winner.
是不是太過了
我是第二名
I know this is a skit, but it should be plausible.
我是第一名
我們的情景設定雖然都是情景劇
(It's not realistic at all.)
-但也不能太過吧 -怎麼了
(Putting on a smart face)
- What's wrong about this? - All right then.
這樣的話
Since you are the Math Olympiad winners,
那麼 那麼
因爲是奧林匹克數學競賽的獲勝者
(Tell us about the Pythagorean theorem.)
please tell us about the Pythagorean theorem.
-麻煩解釋一下勾股定理嗎 -好
Or the quadratic formula. Just anything.
開根公式什麼的
It's not something anyone can understand.
那些不是隨便一個人都能理解的
- What is she talking about? - It's not easy.
說什麼呢
-爲什麼 -不是隨便一個人就能知道的
She says things that aren't relevant to the question.
提問和回答完全是牛頭不對馬嘴
Do you know what an equation is?
-你知道方程式嗎方程式 -人設
You should make it more convincing.
所以說得給合適的人設啊
(She can't proceed with her theme.)
- This is far-fetched. - I know.
給的人設太牽強了
And all we can say about math is an equation and...
因爲是數學方面的
都只知道方程式
- And quadratic formula. - Quadratic formula.
-開根公式 -開根公式
(Bringing all math principles)
What is 3.14?
3.14是什麼
- Pi. - That's enough.
π
- Stop it. - Root.
夠了 夠了
-根號根號根號 -夠了
He's acting as if he knows a lot. My goodness.
好像自己知道很多一樣
你真的
(What?)
- What did you say? - I was talking to myself.
我只是在自言自語
- What was that? - Well...
(He keeps scuffling without teaching anything for 15 years.)
You should speak clearly.
得說敬語纔對啊
- It's my bad. I'm sorry. - You understand?
對不起了
嗯對不起
- Are you a new recruit? - Yes, I'm a newbie.
是新員工嗎
(They're from Running Trading Company.)
是的我們是新員工
So he's your superior.
但是這位是怎麼回事
(Disciplined assistant manager and swaggering new employee)
- That's right. He's my subordinate. - He's an assistant manager.
-沒錯 所以 -代理
這是我們代理 我是新人
And I'm a newbie.
But what kind of assistant manager are you?
什麼代理
- Do you have other work experience? - With your hands in your pockets.
-什麼代理手都不敢插袋不敢插袋 -看來還
I guess you used to be in a different business.
看來還從事其他工作吧
- Right. I made a career change. - I knew it.
我離職了
I was in a different business.
-對吧 -本來是做別的工作
(Assistant Manager Ha, the King of insurance)
That's right. Our company is known for giving a second chance.
沒錯沒錯
我們公司因爲有二次機會而出名
(The new employee)
He has broad shoulders.
肩膀很特別啊
His shoulders look different.
很特別啊真的
That's right. We are gangsters.
沒錯我們是混混公司
- But he looks so nice and kind. - He's nice.
-但是給人印象很善良 -很善良
- He seems good-natured. - They're not intimidating.
給人印象太善良了
(In charge of naiveness, in charge of sinister face)
We're in charge of debt collection.
如果大家有什麼沒收回來的錢可以告訴我
(We can help you with debt collection.)
(Why did people with different jobs gather?)
Today, you guys are here for a package tour.
大家是因爲跟團旅遊聚集在一起的人
(Package tour to Jeju Island)
You are groups of two, and you guys don't know each other.
都是第一次見面來到了濟州島
Now you will take a Running package tour around Jeju Island.
所以打算在濟州島進行R跟團遊
(They will take a package tour around Jeju Island.)
So you should pay for the tour package.
旅行當然需要跟團遊費了
(They have to pay for the tour package.)
You have 50 dollars in your mission bags now.
-現在每人的任務包裏都有五萬韓元 -五萬元
(They all have 50 dollars each.)
- 50 dollars? - You will scatter...
(They can pay as much as they want for the tour package.)
各自分開
and put the amount you are willing to pay in an envelope secretly.
費用交多少完全自願
The mission fund is very important for today's race.
以非公開的形式往信封內裝入參加費
任務費很重要
(The mission fee matters in the race.)
So you should think carefully before you pay.
請考慮清楚提交參加費
Is there the minimum amount we have to pay?
最低費用限制也沒有嗎
(They can pay as much as they want.)
Can I not pay at all?
那不交也可以嗎
It's up to you. Just put the amount you want in an envelope.
自願裝入信封提交就行
(A lot or little? That is the question.)
He's not telling us if we should pay a lot or not.
因爲他沒說到底得多給還是少給
I guess we should pay a reasonable amount.
好像得適當的給
- It might be better to pay a lot. - That might be better.
-多給也有可能是好事 -可能是好事
I think we should pay a lot.
感覺多給比較好
(The newlyweds decided to pay a lot.)
- Make it big. - I was going to do that.
多放點吧
嗯我也打算這樣
(Passing by)
Gosh, I should put some money in here.
哎喲得放點了
- It's very thin. - For this once, I should...
Why did you pay so much?
但是你爲什麼給那麼多
- Do you know something? - Well...
知道些什麼嗎
I thought about it, and if you calculate it mathematically,
我看了一下 按照數學方面來算的話
multiplying it by 2 or 3 should work best.
這個是X2或者是X3左右
- That's nonsense. - "That's nonsense"?
在放狗屁呢
你說我放狗屁嗎
(The human cultural asset speaks in a rough manner.)
Why would a human cultural asset...
哥哥你怎麼能
I paid a moderate amount.
-我適當放了點適當的 -我也適當放了點
(All 8 travelers have paid their entry fees.)
I also paid a moderate amount.
(People who paid a little, People who paid a lot)
You paid a lot.
但是都好像交了很多嘛
I thought we should pay a lot.
好像得多交一點
(Which team will have the upper hand?)
- We collected all entry fees. - Yes.
好 參與費都收到了
Today is the You Must Do Everything...
是的
今天是 被攔住的賭博
(You Must Do Everything If You Get Caught Package Option Trip Race)
If You Get Caught Package Option Trip Race
跟團遊活動旅行競賽
The two people who are on the same package trip are a team today.
一起參與跟團遊的兩人是一組的
(The 2 members joining a package will make a team.)
The entry fee you just submitted...
剛纔提交的參與費
(The entry fee they just submitted...)
(will be their team money.)
will be your team money.
是自己的隊伍的組費
(People who paid a little, People who paid a lot)
You will start your trip with the total amount submitted.
用組內兩人的合計金額來進行今天的旅遊
(They must travel today only with the entry fee they submitted.)
- Yes! - Nice! How much did you pay?
(In other words, it's advantageous to pay a lot.)
You must return the rest of the money.
剩下的錢請都返還回來
(Honey, you did a good job!)
(It's unfavorable for Team Human Cultural Asset...)
I'm in trouble. I didn't pay a lot.
我沒 我沒交很多
How much did you pay?
-我也是 -交了多少
(and Team Running Trading Company from the start.)
- I'm worried. - I also paid quite a bit.
我也只交了一點
The team with the most money is...
提交最多的組是昭旻世燦新婚夫妻
the newlyweds, So Min and Se Chan, who paid 60 dollars.
總共六萬韓元
Why did you pay so much? Did you pay 40 dollars?
哇你怎麼交了那麼多
Next are Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo with 41 dollars.
你交了四萬韓元嗎
還有智孝光洙41000韓元
(Team Olympiad, 41 dollars)
- You almost paid nothing. - They paid 36 and 5 dollars.
姐姐幾乎沒怎麼交嘛
5000韓元和36000韓元 總共41000韓元
I paid a little.
不是的 稍微稍微付了一點
Team Asst. Manager Ha and the New Recruit...
這裏HA代理和新職員隊是5千韓元 5千韓元
(Team Running Trading Company, 10 dollars)
paid 5 dollars each, and have a total of 10 dollars.
- Gosh. - Look at that.
總共1萬韓元
這裏真是
Hey High Schooler, I'll be in your debt after today.
兩人差不多
高中生 要多多關照了
What are you talking about?
什麼話啊
Team Ink-and-Wash Painting Human Cultural Asset and pupil...
這裏的水墨畫非物質文化遺產隊的門徒隊
paid 5 dollars and 2 dollars and have a total of 7 dollars.
是5千韓元 2千韓元 總共7千韓元
(Team Human Cultural Asset, 7 dollars)
Oh, my.
哎喲喂
That's...
-真是 -小氣小氣
(They're amazing in many ways.)
- That's cutting it close. - That's amazing.
You suit each other.
真是了不起了不起
很配啊
(Crawling)
- I'm going to owe you a favor. - He's a real human cultural asset.
要請大家多多關照我了
(Dumbfounded)
- He's a human cultural asset. - I'm going to owe you a favor.
真的是非物質文化遺產啊
真的是非物質文化遺產
What kind of human cultural asset...
多多關照啊
身體力行啊
來濟州島只帶7千韓元
brings seven dollars to Jeju Island?
非物質文化遺產
(The human cultural asset suffering from the hardships of life)
- I'm a human cultural asset. - I'm...
我們可是非物質文化遺產
I'm going to owe you a favor.
讓大家關照一下就行
I brought much more money with me when I was in high school.
因爲是非物質文化遺產
高中時我身上也帶着幾萬韓元來的呢
(They might have to share a bowl of pork and rice soup.)
You could have a bowl of pork and rice soup each, and leave.
喫碗豬肉湯飯再走就行了呢
Today,
來 今天參觀一下我們旅行社準備的路線後
(The mission funds have been given.)
you can go back to Seoul...
after taking the course our travel agency has prepared for you.
(They will travel the course prepared by the staff.)
再回到首爾就行了
There will be all kinds of options and extra fees.
有着各種各樣的選擇和追加費用
(There are all kinds of options and extra fees.)
First, each course has...
首先每個路線都有規定觀光人數
a set number of people that can go sightseeing.
(Each course has a set number of people that can take it.)
Regardless of the teams, that number will be decided...
和小組資金無關 要通過遊戲來決定
(The number will be decided by the games.)
- after playing games. - Okay.
The people who get the chance to go sightseeing...
獲得觀光機會的人
(The members who are going on the trip...)
will be able to enjoy all the course offers limitlessly...
可以盡情享受相應路線中的食物禮物
which includes buying food, gifts, and extra options.
或者另外再選擇購買
(will enjoy all of the course and get a stamp.)
They will get a stamp each during that course.
在相應路線中可以獲得一個圖章
However, for the people excluded from going sightseeing,
但被排除在觀光之外的成員
(Those who were excluded from losing a game...)
one loser will be decided after playing a simple game each time.
那時會通過簡單的任務選出墊底的一人
(will play a game to choose who pays for the course.)
Also, the loser will cover the entire cost of that course...
相應路線的全部費用都要由那組的隊員來支付
using their team money.
(The chosen one will pay the whole price with the team money.)
- They will pay up the whole amount. - We should do our best then.
原來要一次性支付啊
- Your team might end up in debt. - Yes.
努力去做就行了
這裏可能還會是負分啊
(They have different amounts of team money.)
The teams who don't have a lot of money should join forces.
對哦
我們這種有錢的隊伍團結在一起吧
- Okay. - Let's join forces.
-OK OK -好的
- Let's target them. - This is good.
我們一起 團結一心
他們會攻擊我們的
(But the funds will grow larger...)
不錯啊
(to the point in which the difference means nothing.)
- We should also join forces. - Okay.
團結在一起吧
不錯吧
我們也團結在一起吧 姐姐
The top three people who have the most stamps...
-好的 -團結在一起
所以在跟團遊結束時
(The top 3 people who have the most stamps...)
when the package trip is over will get a prize.
圖章數最多的3個人獲得獎品
(will get a prize after the 4 courses.)
- This is regardless of teams. - Really?
和小組資金無關都會送上
(The 2 members of the team with the least team money get a penalty.)
There will be a penalty for the team that has the least team money.
和小組資金無關
但是小組資金最少的人要接受懲罰
- Okay. - Okay.
You could also get the prize and penalty at the same time.
也就是獲得獎品的同時也可能會受罰
Starting now,
來 現在開始
you will have to even pay for the water you drink.
各位哪怕喝一瓶水
(Even a bottle of water will be included in the package fee.)
也會算在我們跟團遊的費用之中
- That's too harsh. - You're tight.
好過分啊
(Running Tour's cheapest package that's known for ripping people off)
I should have drunk some water beforehand.
很嚴格啊
早知道就先喝點水了
The fee you use in the car on the way to the course...
在前往相應路線的車上
(All charges throughout the day will be included in the expense.)
will also be counted.
使用的費用也會全部計算在內
I will give each team their team money and individual stamp passport.
現在發放各隊的小組資金還有各自的圖章護照
(Team Newlyweds, 60 dollars, Team Olympiad, 41 dollars)
(Team Running Trading Company, 10 dollars,)
- Okay. - Oh, my.
好的
(Team Human Cultural Asset, 7 dollars)
The first schedule is...
首先第一個行程
(The first schedule)
- Yes? - the highlight of package trips.
算是跟團遊的亮點對吧
(Forced shopping)
It's forced shopping.
是強制購物
- Shopping? - Forced shopping?
購物
- Okay. - Forced shopping?
強制購物
- They disappeared a lot these days. - Shop with seven dollars?
-不是 -最近已經少了很多
(Human cultural asset with the total fortune of 7 dollars)
-拿着7千韓元去哪裏購物
We will go to a shopping street, a Jeju Island tourist attraction.
我們會去濟州島有名的購物街
(They'll visit Chilseongro Shopping Street.)
Only three people can participate.
可以參加觀光的只有3人
(The number of Forced Shopping participants: 3 people)
The first game is...
來 第一個遊戲
(The first game of Package Option Trip Race)
Noise Complaint Apartment, which we played last time.
就是上次玩過的層間噪音公寓
(Noise Complaint Apartment)
For each round, one team leader must come out,
每一輪每組派出一人
(1 member of each team will come out and pile a hand tower.)
and a total of four team leaders will play the game.
-共四人出戰 -公寓公寓公寓
They will shout the game chant at the same time,
一起呼喊遊戲口號
(They take the bottom hand to slap the top hand.)
and they will use both hands to pile a hand tower after the chant.
口號結束後把雙手都疊起來
(If one makes a sound, he or she loses.)
If you make a sound while getting slapped, you will be out.
然後去拍打 如果發出聲音就淘汰啊
(If no one is eliminated,)
(the one caught at the predetermined floor will be eliminated.)
One person must come from each team.
沒錯
首先每組請先派出一人
- You must go unconditionally. - Gosh.
這一定要由哥來啊
(Jong Kook competes for Team Running Trading Company.)
So Min, you should go first since Jong Kook is there.
昭旻啊 因爲有鍾國哥你先上
(The new groom pushes his wife into the deadly game.)
You should go after Jong Kook.
因爲鍾國哥先上場 所以先由你來
- It hurts. - Jong Kook won't slap you hard.
真的
鍾國哥不會打得很重
Jong Kook won't slap you hard.
會痛啊
鍾國對你不會很用力的
- He won't let me off. - No, he will let you off this time.
哥哥不會讓着我
不會的 這次會讓着你的
(He has no intention on playing it.)
Kwang Soo, do you want to go?
光洙啊 你出來
It doesn't matter.
我沒關係
(The Palm Tyson says, "Welcome.")
可以忍住的
Gosh...
他
(The catfish new groom saves himself.)
- You can do it. - Come out.
-可以做到的 -不行
Shop as much as you want.
-出場吧出場 -去盡情購物吧
You're really despicable.
真是卑鄙 卑鄙
(Jong Kook, Seok Jin, Ji Hyo, and So Min will start Round 1.)
New Recruit Kim, you can do it!
來 金社員加油
While you sing, I will...
-先唱歌 然後由我來 -昭旻啊
- 1, 2. - 1, 2.
(They must win to take the shopping course.)
- 1, 2, 3, 4. - 1, 2, 3, 4.
12 1234
- Cross the starry bridge - Cross the starry bridge
走過灑滿月光的大橋
(The package trip participants know how to have fun.)
- Let's go - Let's go
哎喲哎喲 哎喲哎喲
(Tiger Moth bounce and catfish bounce)
- Let's go - Let's go
哎喲哎喲 哎喲哎喲
- Pass by the windy reed field - Pass by the windy reed field
走過被風吹動的蘆葦地
(The new bride had plenty of trips on a tourist bus.)
- Let's go - Let's go
哎喲哎喲 哎喲哎喲
石三挺有活力
- Seok Sam is energetic. - You always
-不管何時 不管何時 -挺有精氣神的
(Seok Sam is an energetic cultural asset.)
- You always - He's energetic.
Seok Sam is energetic.
石三挺有活力
(Seok Sam's back hunches whenever he's excited.)
- Waited for me at your apartment - Waited for me at your apartment
你的公寓都在等着我
- Let's go - Let's go
哎喲哎喲 哎喲哎喲
- 12th floor! - 12th floor!
-12層 -12層
(If no one makes a sound, the one on the 12th floor is eliminated.)
- Okay. - Okay.
I'm in trouble. My hand is underneath her hand.
出大事了 在她下面
(1st floor, Seok Jin will slap So Min.)
- We will start from the bottom. - Will we start...
GO GO
從下開始
(The person at the bottom slaps the hand at the top.)
- from the bottom? - Start from the 12th floor.
從下面開始打對吧
12層就淘汰哦
You will be eliminated if you make a sound from now on.
現在如果出聲音就淘汰
So Min, endure it.
昭旻啊 撐住
(They will be eliminated if they make a sound from now on.)
(So Min must endure Seok Jin's smashing.)
(Holding it in)
- Gosh, So Min took it. - What happened?
昭旻忍住了
(So Min passed.)
- Who's next? - Second floor.
怎麼回事
好了吧 好了吧
(2nd floor, Ji Hyo will slap Seok Jin.)
2層
- It's my turn to slap, right? - Yes.
是我嗎 是我來打吧
Ji Hyo, let's send him away this time.
姐姐這次送走他
Don't make any sounds.
不要發聲音 不要發聲音
(The Pupil passed.)
- Good job. - Second floor.
忍得好
2層
(And here it comes.)
It's his turn.
來了 來了
(3rd floor, Jong Kook will slap Ji Hyo.)
It's his turn.
- Is it Jong Kook's turn? - It's Jong Kook's turn.
是鍾國哥嗎
- It's over. - Why did you put your hand there?
是鍾國哥 結束了
幹嘛要把手放在那裏啊
(She miscalculated.)
- I didn't know. - Take it.
我不知道呢
Ji Hyo is shrewd, so she's good at holding it in.
又很會忍 因爲智孝很狠
(He succeeded at changing jobs with his sole palm strength.)
(Will Ji Hyo be able to endure his monstrous smashing?)
(Smash)
(Enduring)
- Other people... - I'm in pain.
其他人發聲音
(The impact was delivered to the hand below that.)
- will also be eliminated. - No.
連我都痛啊
不是的不是的
(She held it in.)
- So Min, you must endure it. - How could the pain...
如果其他人發聲音也淘汰哦
昭旻啊 要忍住
怎麼會一直傳到我這裏
also reach me when Ji Hyo was slapped?
明明是姐姐被打啊
(Among 12 floors)
Fourth floor.
現在是4層
We have 10 floors left now.
還剩10層 10層
We have eight floors left.
還剩8層
He's really bad at math.
這哥數學真的好差
- Weren't you in second place? - I was mistaken.
哥 你不是亞軍嘛
(It's obvious that Ji Hyo couldn't tell the mistake either.)
How could you be mistaken?
搞錯了 搞錯了
什麼搞錯了嘛
- Are you a foreigner? - I just got this problem wrong.
是外國人嗎
那時就是答錯了這個問題 所以我是亞軍呀
- That's why. - You can't do addition.
(The math geniuses are especially weak when it comes to subtraction.)
Endure it. Let's go!
加法
忍住忍住忍住
- Send him away. - It's So Min. That was...
送走送走
是昭旻呢 昭旻
(5th floor, Jong Kook will slap So Min.)
(It's the new employee's turn again.)
My palm hurts.
我的手掌好痛
- It's Jong Kook's right hand. - Jong Kook...
鍾國哥是右手呢
(The Tiger Moth bride could be eliminated.)
- Your... - Yes?
哥哥
我們的這個
wife will be eliminated now.
成爲妻子的這位會淘汰的
No, she can endure it.
不會的 可以忍住
- Endure it. - Two people must be eliminated.
忍住
要淘汰兩個人對吧
(I have no choice. It's a game.)
- It can't be helped. - Of course, it's a game.
無可奈何啊
是啊
是遊戲
(Avoiding)
(So Min is out.)
- She avoided him. - She's eliminated.
- She's eliminated. - She's eliminated.
沒打到
淘汰淘汰
(Sobbing)
Why did you make a sound when you weren't even slapped?
淘汰淘汰
都還沒打到幹嘛發出聲音
Good job.
幹得好 幹得好 幹得好
(Being kind)
- Did you see the look in his eyes? - Yes?
你看到他的眼神了嗎
(If you get to know him, the catfish husband is a romanticist.)
- Did you see the look in his eyes? - I thought you were going to die.
你看到哥哥的眼神了嗎
想要把你給幹掉
- Just endure it this once. - I can't watch this.
又要打了又要打了
-我看不下去了 -就一次
(It's Jong Kook's attack and Ji Hyo's defense.)
- I will also... - It will just smart once.
就當做是打針
No. Your bone might break, Ji Hyo.
就刺痛一下 刺痛一下
-就刺痛一下 –不是的 骨頭可能會斷的 姐姐
(She's the olympiad winner who has the most patience.)
It will just hurt once, and it will be over.
稍微刺痛一下結束了
(The Palm Tyson is controlling his breathing.)
The new recruit is angry.
新職員生氣了
(She took her hand out.)
(Shouting)
(The math genius took her hand out at the crucial moment.)
I think you made a sound.
發出聲音了
(Murmuring)
- He made a sound. - Can you take your hand out?
發出聲音了
還可以抽走的嗎
She...
-發出聲音了 -不是這個
這個
(Asking to play the video)
She took her hand out.
可以抽出來嗎
Can you take your hand out?
不是那樣的 因爲打得太用力了
(Seok Sam moaned as it was unexpected.)
She...
-怎麼能抽出來呢  -不是
- Isn't that cheating? - Can you take your hand out?
這不是犯規嗎
(She's not good at subtracting, but she's good at taking her hand out.)
- Can you take your hand out? - She took out her hand.
可以抽出來嗎
不是 打得太用力了啊
My fingers aren't moving "automatically".
這手指它現在都自動了
(Saying he twisted his finger and it's moving on its own)
- Do you mean "automatically"? - What?
-什麼  -自動是什麼啊 哥
- Do you mean "automatically"? - I'm sorry.
自動是什麼啊
(So Min, Ji Hyo, and Seok Jin got eliminated in the first round.)
是吧
鍾國哥這樣也行吧
(Haha, Jae Seok, Kwang Soo, and Se Chan will play in Round 2.)
Okay, the next group should go.
來吧
下一回合的人 下一回合的人
The people who didn't play should come out.
湊熱鬧的人們都出來了啊
- Okay, three people should go. - Se Chan, I can only trust you.
-湊熱鬧的人們 -來吧
世燦啊
3人吧 3人
(They have a chance as they're all weaker members.)
- Don't worry. - Okay.
世燦啊 這一回合就只有你強一點兒了
不要擔心
- You need to do a good job. - You need to do a good job.
有得一比
(Their excitement engine is starting.)
來 開始
-噠啦啦 噠啦啦 -有得一比
- It's doable. - Go
(Go!)
- Let's go - Let's go
嘿喲喂 嘿喲
(Insurance king Assistant Manager Ha is showing off his karaoke skills.)
- Pass by the windy reed field - Pass by the windy reed field
風吹蘆葦蕩
(Bounce)
- Let's go - Let's go
嘿喲喂 嘿喲
- You always... - You always...
無論何時都將我
- 9th floor. - 9th floor. That's it.
9層
9層 行了
(The game of quick hands)
- Let's go. - No, come here.
等下
- Come here. - Come here.
不行 放進來
-放進來 -放進來 放進來
(Hurry up and play.)
- Let's do it quickly. - Do it quickly.
哥 輕鬆地快點兒玩吧
- Let's do it quickly. - Okay.
快點兒吧
-快點兒連續來吧  -等下
等下 等下
(1st floor, Kwang Soo will slap Haha.)
- Okay. - Haha.
最下面是誰 最下面是誰
-來吧 來吧 -來吧
- Who is on the bottom? - It's me.
最下面
(They will get eliminated right away if they make a sound.)
- Hurry up. - Haha's a scardy cat.
是我 是我
別拖時間
因爲都是膽小鬼
Isn't this school violence?
對 都是膽小鬼
- Hurry up. - It won't hurt at all.
一點兒都不痛
快點兒 快點兒
(He uses his long arm to gain momentum.)
It doesn't hurt. It didn't hurt, did it?
一點兒都不痛
不痛
不痛吧
(Enduring)
- Didn't you make a sound? - You're a man.
男人啊 男人啊
不是出聲了吧
(Ordering)
- It's okay, Assistant Manager Ha. - It's okay.
沒事兒 HA代理 沒事兒
我們忍得挺好的
HA代理 沒事兒
Wait a minute, Recruit Kim,
我們代理沒事兒
等下 金社員 你是社長嗎
are you the owner?
(The new recruit is full of a sense of ownership.)
- It's okay, Assistant Manager Ha. - Okay.
不是 不是
是社長嗎
沒事兒 沒事兒
I thought you were the owner.
來吧 來吧
-還以爲是領導  -來吧
(2nd floor, Jae Seok will slap Kwang Soo.)
- Do it. - Okay, the second floor should go.
如何 好
(Now, it's for the human cultural asset to smash.)
- Okay. - Let's go.
來 2層來吧
(He's really scared of the thought of getting slapped.)
At first, I had no idea how it will be.
好的 來吧
一開始
-現在完全無法反應  -啊 3層嗎
Is it still the third floor? Whose turn is it? Who will slap now?
是3層嗎
是誰呀 誰打呀
(The representative scaredy-cats are gathered, so the game's quite slow.)
- He's the human cultural asset. - Of course.
是人類文化遺產
(Should I slap him or not?)
果然
(Along with his wrist movements trained from...)
- He has a different rhythm. - He's rhythmical.
不一樣 節奏不一樣
(ink-and-wash paintings, everyone is bouncing along with his rhythm.)
They became really close to each other.
是HipHop HipHop
變親近很多啊
The four of them became really close to each other.
四人變親近很多
(The hip-hop waterwheel is suddenly turning.)
- Bam - Bam
噹噹噹
棒棒棒棒棒棒
- Beat everyone - Beat everyone
碾壓 棒棒
- Bam - Bam
棒棒棒棒棒棒
(The 4 scaredy-cats are using all kinds of methods to buy time.)
- Beat everyone - Beat everyone
真是的
碾壓
(He starts slapping after preparing for a long time.)
- Let's go. - They're finally doing it.
-來吧 -有得一比
(In pain)
(Frowning)
That was intense.
很大勁兒 很大勁兒 很大勁兒
(He succeeds at defending while giving his face up.)
很大勁兒啊
- That was intense. - It didn't hurt at all.
-是吧  -是的
-很大勁兒 很大勁兒 -一點兒都不痛
- What floor are we on? - You have six floors left.
我們現在几几幾 幾層來着
(They have 6 floors left among 9 floors.)
- What floor are we on? - You're on the sixth floor.
還需要6層
-還有幾層啊  -還有6層
還有6層 剛那是第2層
(Se Chan smashes his hand on Jae Seok's hand.)
- Se Chan. - Endure it.
世燦啊
忍住 忍住
That's it. You can endure it.
是的 能忍住
(Let's endure it.)
It doesn't hurt.
厲害啊
Everyone is so well-behaved.
很安靜啊
- Okay, next. - Seventh floor.
好的 下一個
7層
(Se Chan must endure Kwang Soo's right hand.)
It's Kwang Soo's right hand this time.
呀 光洙很嚇人 光洙很嚇人
He's going to use his right hand.
-右手出來了  -要用右手打
Se Chan, endure it.
(The math genius high school student is merciless.)
- He's merciless. - Let's fly away.
世燦 忍住啊
是無血無淚的朋友
(Be proud.)
You can't lose to a high school student.
要打飛 要打飛 要打飛
不能輸給高中生
(The sound is extraordinary.)
You must endure it.
得大力打啊
(Kwang Soo just slapped Se Chan using his fist.)
He slapped with his fist.
用拳頭打的
(He doesn't want to lose, so he endured it with clenched teeth.)
等下
用拳頭打的
- You're going to be eliminated. - Why did you slap with your first?
等下
你是想咋的
(Upset)
用拳頭打的 用拳頭打的
When did I?
怎麼了 大叔
- Young punk! - Why?
喂 你這毛頭小子啊
(He got slapped by a high school student on his honeymoon.)
How dare you slap me...
怎麼了啊
竟敢打哥哥
- Why are you hitting me? - with your fist?
-竟然用拳頭  -用拳頭打啊
How dare you slap me with your fist?
喂 用拳頭打嗎
(The high school student's character hasn't developed completely yet.)
- Right now, you... - Is that not allowed?
喂 你現在
Shouldn't he be eliminated?
那樣不行嗎 不行嗎
那啥 淘汰了吧
- He's eliminated. - He's eliminated.
淘汰了啊
淘汰了
(Kwang Soo is eliminated from offending people by using his fist.)
Why?
我淘汰了嗎
- No wonder, even I was hurting. - He's eliminated.
-這得淘汰了啊 -淘汰啊 難怪我都覺得痛
Even I was hurting.
這樣打的
(The last 9th floor, Haha will slap Jae Seok.)
If Jae Seok makes a sound, Haha will win.
如果HAHA在這兒讓人出聲的話
(If Jae Seok makes a sound, Jae Seok will be eliminated.)
If Jae Seok doesn't make a sound, Jae Seok will win.
就是那人淘汰
不出聲的話 就是HAHA當選
(If Jae Seok endures it, Haha will be eliminated.)
- Oh, I will be okay then. - That's right.
被淘汰啊
哦 我沒事兒啊
(He smiles while showing his gums.)
- You will be okay. - You did a good job.
是的
-OK  -做得好 做得好
Look at Jae Seok right now.
等下
-現在在錫哥  -在錫哥
Look at the face of the human cultural asset.
忍住 忍住
看來也是人啊 看看那表情啊
(No Pain Master Yu is summoned.)
You should slap him hard.
忍住
看來是人啊
打大勁兒點兒吧
- I do not know pain. - Lay it down hard.
痛苦
-大勁兒  -打大勁兒點兒吧
(The result depends on the final slap.)
He might wet himself.
我不知道痛苦的
哦 有打過架啊
- Just do it already. - Get it over with.
快打吧
快打吧 看不下去了
I can't watch!
看不下去了
- Darn it hurts. - It wasn't a direct hit.
噠啊
-歪掉了 -啊 好痛
(Haha slaps and gets eliminated.)
Haha, you're out.
HAHA淘汰
- It wasn't a direct hit. - He only hurt his own hand.
打歪了
(The human cultural asset endured the pain with willpower.)
好走
- Haha, you're out. - It wasn't a direct hit.
歪掉了
HAHA淘汰
(It's over, right?)
- He only hurt his own hand. - It slipped.
打歪了
-打歪了 -自己痛
Unbelievable.
結束
真是的
(Foul language)
@#$#!@%$#%呀
(Thankfully, the airplane flies over them at the right time.)
(Everyone's happy to film near an airport.)
- It wasn't a direct hit. - A plane is flying over us.
啊 飛機飛過了啊
飛機
(They're able to resolve their anger at any time.)
I'm good now.
行了
He's good.
發泄了
(Jeju Airport honors the human cultural asset's status.)
Perfect timing.
時機很好
Nice timing!
- It was nothing. - We couldn't hear a thing.
-那是哥喊來的嗎  -果然是人類文化遺產
不是的 不是的
(Call us when you're angry.)
You heard wrong.
-因爲是哥喊來的  -完全不是那樣的
(Jong Kook, Jae Seok, and Se Chan will go to the shopping course.)
The three will go shopping...
好的 因此3人將去購物
and one out of the rest...
剩下5人中1人
(1 of these 5 members...)
將用小組資金結算所有購物金額
will pay for the expenses from the team's budget.
(will pay for it using the team money.)
Just so you know, Jong Kook is quite the spender.
我們金社員有點兒浪費力的
(Let's head off to see Jong Kook waste money.)
I'm unleashing my shopaholic side.
是的 我今天要狂買
Let's get going then.
好的 那麼咱們去吧
(Let's head off to see Jong Kook waste money.)
Sure, let's head to the van.
好的 我們去乘車吧
Let's go.
好的
走吧
Come on.
(The highlight of a package tour, forced shopping)
Hello.
請進吧
- It's good to see you. - Shopping...
-幸會 -購物嗎
While on the trip,
好的 各位
(The service on the bus for a pleasant package trip)
我們旅行期間
- you could get hungry or thirsty. - Right.
可能會餓
-也可能會渴啊 -是的
That's why we prepared coffee, beverages, and water.
所有我們準備了
(Various drinks and snacks are available.)
罐裝咖啡 各種飲料 純淨水
- Coffee too? - Chips, chocolate, jelly...
咖啡好
餅乾 巧克力 軟糖 三明治
are prepared for you too.
都有的
Beverages will cost three dollars...
飲料類都是3,000韓元
while the snacks are five dollars.
小喫類都是5,000韓元
Whatever you buy will be added to the tab...
喫多少累積多少金額
(What they eat will be accumulated,)
which will be paid by the one paying...
都由第一個路線結算的人一起結算
(and the person to pay for the first course will pay for it.)
- for the first schedule. - Really?
-第一個嗎  -是的
- Hold on. - Which will be paid...
那麼
都由第一個路線結算的人一起結算
(One will pay for everything.)
- Really? - Yes.
-第一個嗎  -是的
(Jae Seok, Jong Kook, and Se Chan)
That means the three of us can eat whatever we want.
那麼挺好啊
我們三直接喫就行了吧
If your teammate has to pay,
是的
但如果自己組的被逮住的話
(But one of their teammates might have to pay.)
then it'll take a toll on you too.
自己租的錢就沒了
(Jee Seok Sam, Pupil, spends more money than he has)
There's nothing more to life anyway.
那啥 人生有啥呀
是吧
We'll think of the consequences later.
得先用啊
- We'll get going then. - Sure.
出發啦
好的
Can I get a bag of chips?
那啥 請給一袋餅乾吧
(Starting)
How about some coffee?
好的
我們也來一杯咖啡吧
- Should we have some coffee? - Please get So Min some coffee.
咖啡 喝咖啡吧
-請給我們一人一杯咖啡吧 -好的
I'd like a refreshing beverage too.
請給我們涼快的吧
- Coffee... - That'll be three dollars each.
給點兒咖啡吧
喝的是3,000韓元
(Adding 3 dollars each)
- Sure. - They're not cheap.
好的 好的
是挺厲害的
Is there a cup too?
有水杯嗎
- One with ice. - Nice.
那啥 有水杯嗎
給我冰杯 冰杯
This will be three dollars too.
這是3,000韓元
(It's 3 dollars for a cup of ice?)
- Sure thing. - This too?
這是3,000韓元
-水杯也是3,000韓元嗎  -是的
- Just hand it out. - Can I get some jelly too?
水杯也是嗎
(Enjoying the service)
- I'd like some ice too. - Black coffee.
也給軟糖吧
老公 我也要冰杯
A cup of ice, please!
冰杯啊
給一個冰杯
Black coffee.
-哎喲 是來觀光的啊  -給一個冰杯
(Adding 3 dollars each)
- Unbelievable. - This chance might not come again.
-哎喲 都亂套了  -就是這時候用的啊
(The payments are added as they keep order.)
That's for me.
我要那個
- This... - Go ahead.
好的
可以用信用卡嗎
Thank you.
-給我餅乾吧 -好的
Can you get that for me?
謝謝
喂 你能接下這個嗎
(Team Human Cultural Asset has 7 dollars.)
We shouldn't be stingy when on a vacation.
謝謝
來旅遊就是要這麼用錢的
- Exactly. - Nicely said.
當然了
好喫
This is the reason we save money up.
就是爲了這時候用才存錢的
(Worried)
Everyone's spending money like crazy.
哎喲 用的
Are there any chips?
餅乾
有餅乾嗎 餅乾
I'll get some to you.
給你
You're eating a lot today.
喫很多啊
今天喫得挺多啊
Shouldn't you stop?
看來來得挺急的啊
(He spends like he has 700 million dollars.)
- All right! - Can we stop eating now?
看來餓了啊
來
One team might start off as bankrupt.
不是 哥 別吃了
那啥 一開始就有組完蛋的話
We don't know who'll have to pay, so let's eat.
就喫吧 不知道會是誰啊
不知道會是誰出啊
- Unbelievable. - This is wrong.
怎麼喫得怎麼多
不管了
(They've spent 63 dollars.)
You've spent 63 dollars.
-現在累計有6萬3千韓元  -什麼
One team will go bankrupt.
-好的 給你 -這會完蛋的
(Not worrying about the amount)
- For sure. - No matter which team pays,
是的
這會完蛋的
- it will be a lot. - One team will go bankrupt.
無論哪組被逮住 都完蛋了
Any team will go bankrupt.
只要被逮住就完了
真的 無論哪個隊被逮住都會破產
(Seok Sam spends like it's gambling.)
As long as it's not our team.
只要不是我就行
That's just how it is.
不是那樣的嗎
(Unique taste)
Don't you have any sweet or savory snacks?
那個 有味同*或者魷魚球嗎
So tell me. What's your dream?
有味同*
(Out of the blue)
你夢想是什麼
That's right. What's your dream?
-我呢  -是的 你夢想是什麼
- It's to be a scientist. - A scientist?
我的夢想是科學家
Whose your favorite scientist?
-科學家嗎  -是的
有尊敬的科學家嗎
Nobel?
諾貝爾嗎
- Einstein. - Who?
愛因
- Nobel. - Einstein.
諾貝爾嗎
諾貝爾 諾貝爾
Honey, what was your dream growing up?
愛因斯坦
老公 老公的夢想是什麼
- Me? - He's my mentor.
我嗎
是我的導師
My dream was to meet a pretty lady...
就是遇到美人
- Then your dream came true. - and live with her forever.
-生活是我的夢想  -老公
老公夢想實現了啊
No, not quite.
還不夠
(Darn it.)
我去
(As they eat, they arrive at the first course.)
- So we're at our first location. - Right.
好的 各位
就要到我們第一處購物街了
Yes, let's spend some money!
好的
好的 得去揮霍下啊
(Chilseongro, a shopping district in Jeju with a long history)
I'm going to buy you a few things.
要給你買幾個嗎
This is life, I guess.
-你就隨便買吧  -嗯
(Including Sanjicheon and Jejumok Government Office,)
- Right. - I'll spend at least 1,000 dollars.
今天要花錢
今天要揮霍
(the shopping district connects us to various tourist attractions.)
The three of you...
3位可以購物10分鐘
(They're given 10 minutes to shop.)
will have 10 minutes to shop...
無所謂是給自己買還是給別人買禮物
(They can shop freely to vitalize the local economy.)
for yourself or your teammate.
The three of you will get off now.
3位下車
(The 3 members will get off.)
- Can we go shopping now? - Yes.
-真讓我們去購物啊  -是的
Please put on your masks.
請戴上口罩
- Mr. Kim. - Yes?
-金社員 -在
Buy something for my daughter, will you?
拜託買下我們小song的衣服
Your daughter?
小song的衣服啊
Human cultural asset,
-那文化遺產先生   -嗯嗯
- can you get me something too? - Okay.
也拜託就給我買一件吧
OK OK
拜託啦
(They head out after receiving various requests.)
Let's go shopping then.
好的 那去購物吧
- Hello. - Hello.
啊 好的 您好
Hello, everyone!
您好
哎喲 您好
(Big spender Mr. Yang arrives at the shopping district.)
I'm here to spend some money.
您好
我來花錢的
哎喲喂 我來花錢的
I'm here to spend money.
I need to buy clothes for Haha's daughter.
得給HAHA代理買小孩衣服
(The human cultural asset...)
Hello.
您好
(has ladies coming up to greet him in a heartbeat.)
劉在錫 您好
見到您很高興
哎喲喂 哎喲喂
- Hello, everyone. - Hi!
-您好 您好  -您好
(The human cultural asset pleases his fans.)
Hello.
見到您很高興
Hi.
-您好  -您好
(He's warmly welcomed into a clothing store.)
Hold on a second.
等下啊
有啥
Hello.
哎喲 您好
(He picks a cardigan that suits the modernized hanbok.)
Is it for your pupil?
要給門徒的嗎
Can you get me something too?
請給我買一個
No, it's for me.
不是 是我要穿的
Why would I get my pupil anything?
爲什麼給門徒
(The pupil is trained under harsh circumstances.)
- Guys. - Yes?
-各位 -嗯
(They will choose who will pay for everything.)
We will now see...
我們現在要選定1個結算人
- who pays for everything. - Sure.
(Random silent games)
You'll play a series of random silent games.
以沉默的隨機遊戲
(They will play a variety of silent games.)
Quite a few of them actually.
進行各種沉默遊戲
(Silent 007)
Silent 007,
沉默的007砰
Silent 3, 6, 9,
或者沉默的369 或者沉默的詞語接龍
(Silent 3, 6, 9)
(Silent Word Chain)
or Silent Word Chain.
You will choose the game you wish to play.
選擇想玩的沉默遊戲
- How do you play Silent Word Chain? - Silent Word Chain?
-不說話怎麼做詞語接龍 -詞語接龍
(In Silent Word Chain, body language will be used.)
You'll explain the words with body language.
用動作說明單詞就行
- Nice. - Like "bicycle"...
厲害了 這肯定有意思
This sounds like fun.
(One gets a point if one loses or makes a sound.)
If you lose the round or get it wrong,
這時 在遊戲中失敗或者發出聲音
you'll be met with a punishment.
就要被打背部且得分
(The person with the highest points will pay.)
The one with the highest number of points will pay.
分數最高的人要去結算
You'll now fall silent.
現在開始沉默
(Silent random games begin.)
And go.
開始
(Kwang Soo will go first.)
Starting with Kwang Soo, you'll play your desired game.
從李光洙開始想玩的遊戲吧
(Silent 3, 6, 9)
(Clap)
(Silent 3, 6, 9 isn't that difficult.)
(There aren't any hitches so far.)
(Clap, Clap)
(Clap!)
(We knew the pupil would mess up first.)
Wrong!
錯
Pound on his back.
打背部
Seok Jin receives a point.
池石鎮1分
(He doesn't know what he got wrong.)
(They switch it up to Silent 007 next.)
(0)
(07 bang!)
(Argh! Argh!)
(0)
(07 bang!)
(Argh! Argh!)
(0)
(07 bang!)
(Argh! Argh! Argh?)
(Why would the pupil raise his hands?)
Seok Jin got it wrong.
池石鎮中招
(Seok Sam gets it wrong twice in a row.)
Seok Jin now has two points.
池石鎮2分
(Let's slow down a bit.)
(The speed is too fast for the pupil.)
Slowly.
(Seok Sam needs time to adjust.)
(We'll go with Silent Word Chain.)
(We'll go this way.)
(Hopping)
(Frog noted.)
(Frog)
(A word that starts with the Korean syllable "ri")
(He's delicately describing a ribbon.)
(Ribbon noted.)
(Easy, right?)
(What on earth was that?)
(You didn't get it?)
Ji Hyo.
宋智孝
(Blinking)
(Come on!)
3, 2, 1.
3 2 1
(Time's up and Ji Hyo receives a point.)
Ji Hyo receives a point too.
宋智孝淘汰 1分
(They already spent 400 dollars.)
The three already spent 400 dollars while shopping.
現在突破40萬韓元了
(Se Chan takes his time.)
Can a woman wear this too?
均碼 這女生可以穿的嗎
I'll buy one for So Min.
一件是給昭旻的
(The newlywed buys an item for his wife.)
(A couple's sweatshirts)
Meanwhile, I'll buy this for myself.
然後我要這個
I'll take this one.
請給我這個
(A familiar song plays.)
Sure.
Seriously?
這麼突然
("Hapjeong Station, Exit Five" by the human cultural asset)
(Chorus by newlywed Yangsebari)
All right, come on!
嘿喲 嘿喲 請給我這兩個
I'll take two!
I'm here to spend money, people.
我今天來花錢了
(He seems to have an experience of being in a chorus.)
嘿喲 嘿喲
How much have I spent so far?
今天 現在多少錢了
Your total is at 180 dollars.
18萬韓元
180 dollars? I'll take one that 20 dollars then!
再給我一個2萬韓元的吧
(Receipt, a total of 200 dollars)
I'll spend a total of 200 dollars.
20萬韓元 結算
(He goes big by spending 200 dollars.)
Since it's winter, I should get something warm.
冬天要來了 給買些暖和的吧
(Jong Kook picks a gift for Haha's daughter.)
How adorable.
這樣的
好可愛
(He repeats, "It's cute.")
I'll take this one. Look how cute it is.
這個 給我這個吧
(He isn't even checking the price.)
好可愛 好可愛
How adorable.
可愛 可愛
I'm glad I have all these gifts for Haha's daughter.
能給我們Song送禮物
(Uncle Jong Kook goes big to help small businesses.)
(Receipt, jumper, woolen hat, and boots for Haha's daughter)
(A total of 200 dollars)
This is great.
真好啊
(The human cultural asset values the fit of clothes.)
Let me see.
我看看
(He's also finished shopping.)
- I'll take this then. - Sure thing.
請給我這個
好 請過來這邊
- Can I get an unopened one? - Sure.
-包一件新的 -好
(He bought some products, and he gets worried.)
So everything we buy...
這樣買走的話 墊底隊要結算嗎
will be paid for by the losing team?
Oh, dear.
糟糕了啊
(Seok Jin 2 points, So Min 1 point, and Ji Hyo 1 point)
The points are 2, 1, and 1.
現在是2比1比1
This will be the last game you play.
最後再來一局
If the two don't get it wrong, will I end up paying?
如果在此結束就是我輸了嗎
That's right.
是的
(He might have to pay 600 dollars when he only has 7.)
- I'll kick off the word chain. - Sure.
那我先給一個提示詞
So Min will go first.
從全昭旻開始
(Silent Word Chain Given word: Jean)
The first word is "jean."
牛仔褲
(A Korean word that starts with the syllable "ji")
(Worm)
(A Korean word that starts with the syllable "yi")
(Teeth)
(Teeth noted.)
(A Korean word that starts with the syllable "bbal")
Seok Jin, you're up.
石鎮
(- Let's act dumb. - Sure thing.)
(The Korean word that starts with the syllable "bbal"!)
(I don't get it.)
(Being as frustrated as he is,)
(he starts rubbing his clothes.)
(Poor Seok Jin)
(Kwang Soo still acts dumb.)
(Are you still going to play dumb?)
(Laundry noted.)
Noted.
認可
(The Korean word that starts with the syllable "rae")
(He calmly starts expressing the word that begins with "rae.")
(Haha gets it right away.)
(This seems to be what he's describing.)
(Everyone seems to get it.)
Kwang Soo, you're out.
李光洙 淘汰
("Re" not "Rae)
That begins with the Korean syllable "re."
那個是re
(Embarrassed)
It wasn't the correct syllable.
洗衣服
(It serves you right for teasing others!)
- "Rae" was the correct syllable. - "Rae" not "re."
-ae ae -洗衣服是這個啊
(The math genius lacks in the language department.)
ae
- It's "rae." - Really?
-ae -是re 水泥車是re
(Final score: Seok Jin 2, So Min 1, Ji Hyo 1, Kwang Soo 1)
What you described starts with "re."
And my word ended with "rae."
洗衣服是rae啊
- It was the wrong syllable? - Goodness.
不是水泥車嗎
(Jong Kook finished shopping.)
- Rae. - It was "rae."
哎喲
-是re -是re
- We'll conclude the game. - Okay.
-結束遊戲了 -OK
- Sure. - You're back.
(New Recruit Kim spent a lot on the presents for Haha's daughter.)
- Look. - You bought a lot.
哎喲
-買了很多啊 -當然
- Sure. - You bought a lot.
I bought a full set.
-買了很多啊 哥哥 -我買了一套
(Running Trading Company is harmonious.)
My gosh, that's heavy.
哎喲 謝謝
- Are you serious? - Sure. I bought a full set.
-給Song的 -真的嗎
當然 一套
(The shopping list makes them smile.)
- He's open-handed. - I also bought shoes.
員工
- My goodness. - That looks great.
-外套 -哎喲
好好看 怎麼辦
- It's adorable. - It's so pretty.
好可愛 好好看
(Anticipating)
I wonder what the human cultural asset bought.
我們非物質文化遺產會買回來什麼呢
(Jae Seok and Se Chan finish shopping.)
Is this enough?
怎樣 好了嗎 怎樣
- He also bought something good. - Show us.
哥哥也買了好東西啊
Thank you.
哥買了什麼
哎喲 謝謝
- This is crazy. - I appreciate it.
真的不得了
-哎喲 謝謝 -我
- I bought a cardigan. - For who? Is it for me?
我買了一件開衫
(Blocking)
It's for me.
誰的 我的嗎
我的
I bought a cardigan which was 199 dollars.
買給自己的嗎
19萬9千韓元的開衫
(Seok Sam wants clothes from the secular world.)
Good. That's the exact amount.
價格剛好啊
You bought one expensive item.
-是貴的 -買了個貴東西啊
Sure. I got a good one.
買了個不得了的
- Honey, what did you buy? - I bought a lot.
老公 買了什麼回來
我買了很多
(A lot of goods)
You should buy things for me.
老公 只買我的就行啊
He bought them for real.
-分碼數 -真的買回來了啊
You should wear this.
-買了什麼 -你先穿一個吧
You should buy things only for me.
只買我的就行啊 老公
(He bought grey sweatsuit...)
- And this is... - A sweatsuit? My gosh.
-運動服 -運動服
-我的 -你這個sense真的
(for the honeymoon.)
How could he buy...
你現在
這個sense
- Just wear it. - But this is...
穿上吧
老公 這衣服
(It's a newlywed couple rally uniform.)
- This is... - Is this a team uniform?
還有這個
-是隊服嗎 -隊服
A team uniform? And this is for the pupil.
這是給門徒的
Thank you.
謝謝
(As he receives the unexpected gift,)
Did you buy something for Seok Sam?
還給門徒買了嗎
(he can't stop smiling.)
This is...
這個
- Seok Sam must be happy. - Seok Sam, that's cute.
真羨慕石三
石三 好可愛
I bought a shirt for him.
想讓他穿件亮色的
- That's nice. - I need something that's worth...
我就買了一件
真好 真好
-這是睡衣嗎 -18萬韓元
(He bought a cute shirt for 20 dollars.)
- 20 dollars. - It's a shirt.
-不是 -再給我一個2萬韓元的吧
This is nice.
是襯衫
-很好啊 -很好啊
(That's how he speaks when he doesn't like something.)
- It's pretty. - I love this shirt. It's cute.
好看
-我喜歡 -很可愛很可愛
I'll tell you about the amount.
真的很可愛啊
先說一下金額
(63 dollars for the bus, 599 dollars for shopping)
The transportation cost is 63 dollars.
剛剛在車內的服務金額63000韓元
And the amount spent on shopping is 599 dollars.
-嗯 -嗯
購物金額599000韓元
- So it's 662 dollars in total. - My goodness.
哎喲喂
-總計66萬2千韓元 -我的天哪
The person who will pay 662 dollars is...
結算66萬2千韓元的人
What do we do?
怎麼辦
(Jee Seok Jin)
- Jee Seok Jin. - My gosh.
是池石鎮
OK
- Jee Seok Jin. - My gosh.
是池石鎮
OK
(Staring at him sharply)
We can do better next time.
下次好好做吧
- We can do better next time. - That's a lot of money.
-下次好好做吧 -好可惜
(The second course begins immediately.)
Let me tell you about the second course.
馬上說明第二個路線
- Okay. - Good.
-很好 -很好
(Blaming)
Why are you so bad at playing games?
OK
怎麼這麼不會玩遊戲
You should try it yourself. They are so good.
不是 你坐這裏看看
-他們 -坐這裏看看
- "You should try it yourself." - They play games so quickly.
坐這裏看看
不是 哪有007遊戲玩那麼快的
There's no way I can beat them.
這樣做是要怎麼玩嘛
(From painting to 007 game, Seok Sam has a lot to learn.)
The second course is the best photo zone on Jeju Island.
第二個遊戲是濟州島的
(The second course is...)
人生美照拍攝區
(the photo zone for the photo of a lifetime.)
That sounds great.
真好
(There are spots for the photo of a lifetime...)
It has a lovely view.
景色真美
(along the beach.)
That's nice.
真好
(They have to play well this time to take the photo of a lifetime.)
We've found many good places.
-我們找到了很好看的地方 -油菜花
- I want to see rapeseed flowers. - Okay.
-有油菜花的 -是嗎
And the next game is...
這次的遊戲是喂 是我
(The second game, Hello, It's Me)
- Hello, It's Me. - What?
- Hello, it's me - Is it about this song?
是什麼
-喂 是我 這個嗎 -是我
(Is the game about making a phone call?)
- How are you doing there - How are you doing there
-你過得好嗎 -你過得好嗎
(She's tearing up.)
(A chance to take the photo of a lifetime depends on this game.)
It's a team game.
以隊戰進行
Each team will select a player to make a phone call.
每隊選定給家人或熟人打電話的1人
(Each team will select a player to make a phone call.)
- And? - You can make a call...
然後呢
-也就是一個人的家人或者朋友 -熟人
(You can make a call to your family or friend.)
- To a friend? - to your family or friend.
給這個人打電話
And one of you will talk on the phone pretending to be the player.
其他人六人中的一人假裝是這個人接電話
(The other person will talk on the phone for 3 minutes.)
(Estimate the time until the person on the line realizes it.)
- I'm in trouble. - And you shouldn't get caught.
-糟糕了 -越快被發現就是不好的
- If I get caught quickly, I lose? - Right.
-越快被發現就是不好的嗎 -是
(If your acquaintance realizes that it's not you, it's the best.)
So if they say, "What's wrong? Is it really you?"
-那麼 -給爸爸打
- Then I lose. - Exactly.
怎麼了 是你嗎
-聽到這些就是不行了吧 -或者媽媽
(If the person on the phone sounds suspicious, you fail.)
- "Who is this?" - I should call my brother.
是的
什麼啊
If the person on the phone sounds suspicious, you fail.
-我肯定要打給媽媽 -如果明顯懷疑了的話
那就馬上結束
(They decide whom to call.)
First, you need to decide whom to call.
各隊先討論決定打給誰吧
- I should call my dad. - I'll call Se Hyeong.
得打給爸爸纔行
我要打給世炯哥
(Listening)
- One from each team will call. - How do you call your dad?
-兩人中一個人打就行 -要怎麼對爸爸說
(So Min's going to call her dad who knows her voice.)
- "Dad." I just do this. - Who should we call?
爸爸 這樣
爸爸
Hang on. Who should we call?
-打給誰呢 -秀晶前輩
等一下 我們選誰呢
Who should it be?
打給誰呢
Should I call my wife?
打給妻子吧 我妻子
(Shall we?)
- She will notice it immediately. - She will.
嫂子應該會馬上發現吧
肯定馬上發現
(They're all thinking about whom to call.)
When we tried, we got caught in less than a minute.
我們都被發現了 一分鐘都不到
Really? How did they know?
真的嗎
-嗯 都被發現了 -怎麼被發現的
But...
但是
(Then he receives a call.)
- Hey. - I wasn't like that.
-這得說出來啊 -我沒說啊
My wife is calling me. Do you want to try talking to her?
妻子打電話來了 你來接看看吧
(He got a call from Chaser.)
- Really? - Just talk to her. Don't whisper.
是嗎
真實的來 不要小聲說
(For a practice, Jae Seok answers Chaser's call.)
- Just talk to her. Don't whisper. - Let me try.
真實的來 不要小聲說
You don't have to whisper. Stay quiet.
我來試試看
不要小聲說 來試試看
-來吧 -安靜些
Where are you, honey?
老婆在哪
- Seok Jin? - Where are you?
哥哥
在哪
I was surprised by your voice.
哎喲 你的聲音嚇我一跳
(Was she surprised?)
I was surprised by your voice.
哎喲 你的聲音嚇我一跳
I thought it was someone else. I'm on my way home now.
還以爲是其他人呢
這要結束走人了
- Where are you going? - Home.
去哪
(Upon the start, Jae Seok overcomes the crisis.)
回家
Did you have a nice day?
今天怎樣 打得好嗎
Gosh, you're Jae Seok.
哎喲 看來是在錫哥哥啊
(He gets caught only in 10 seconds.)
Gosh, you're Jae Seok.
哎喲 看來是在錫哥哥啊
(Happy)
(After a few words, she catches the altered voice.)
Jae Seok, my gosh.
哥 在錫哥
- How did she know? - How did she know?
怎麼知道的
-怎麼知道的 -好感動
How did she know? Su Jung, how did you know?
-你怎麼知道 -這好感動
-秀晶啊 你怎麼知道的 -怎麼知道的
(Jae Seok sounds just like you.)
He sounded just like you.
和在錫哥哥的語調太像了
(It was a low-quality voice alteration.)
I know. So you like your husband's voice better, right?
是吧 果然
還是丈夫的聲音好多了吧
- Sure. - I knew it.
當然啦
(Seok Jin's couple is sweet.)
My gosh.
是吧是吧
-但是嫂子爲什麼成追擊者了 -嫂子
But why is your wife saved as Chaser?
Su Jung.
(It's a sweet but scary name.)
- I didn't know that. - Don't say that.
-這是什麼啊 -安靜些 別說了
(His lone chase got caught.)
- Why is your wife a chaser? - It's just...
是推奴嗎
嫂子爲什麼是追擊者
不是 那個
- Okay. - Su Jung.
-嗯 好 -嫂子
(I can't believe it's Chaser.)
- She's saved as Chaser. - You should change it to runaway.
備註寫的是追擊者
改成逃跑者吧 嫂子
Su Jung.
-好 秀晶啊 -逃跑者
Why are you with them? Are you shooting the show?
嗯 知道了
怎麼都在一起呢 今天有錄製嗎
- We're filming... - She didn't know we were shooting.
-錄節目 -不知道是在錄節目
(She didn't know about the shoot.)
Why are you with them? Are you shooting the show?
怎麼都在一起呢 今天有錄製嗎
- We're filming - She didn't know.
-錄節目 -不知道是在錄節目
She didn't know that. My gosh.
不知道
- She thought you were home. - We're shooting Running Man now.
以爲哥在家嗎
(Giving update)
- She thought Seok Jin was at home. - Su Jung.
嫂子 我們正在拍Running Man
可能以爲哥在家裏呢
(He came to Jeju Island on the day of the shoot.)
喂 我們結束通話吧
Let's stop talking.
Hey.
喂
Are they separated or what?
什麼情況 是表面夫妻嗎
(The longer the call gets, the deeper he's wounded.)
The more we talk, the more I feel hurt.
-哥 -哥 爲什麼會這樣
通話越久傷得越深
- Okay. - Bye.
是分居嗎
-嗯 -嗯 好 掛了
(He ends the call with his wife...)
I'll see you later, Su Jung.
嫂子 下次再見
(by telling her about his business trip to Jeju Island.)
- Bye. - Bye.
-謝謝 -嫂子
Drive safely.
小心開車
(It was a practice, but it's a bummer.)
- She fell for it at first. - She didn't know.
開頭騙過去來着
(The faster the acquaintance notices, the better.)
But she recognized you right away.
-騙過去了 -騙過去了
-馬上發現了 -球打得開心嗎
- Only in three seconds. - That was funny.
3秒就
- Who should we call? - She has quick wits.
-誰來 誰來 -眼特別尖
(So Min will call her dad.)
I'll call my dad, and Ji Hyo will talk to him.
-那我給爸爸打電話 姐姐來 -爸爸 好
Ji Hyo.
智孝姐來
(The faster her dad notices, the better for Team Newlyweds.)
But Ji Hyo's voice is...
可是智孝的聲音
- Ji Hyo has a unique voice. - Gosh, this is...
-智孝的聲音太 -這個
There's no one in the world who sounds like Ji Hyo.
不過 智孝姐姐這種聲音全世界只有一個
(Will Ji Hyo be able to talk on the phone for a long time?)
Are you making a call right away? Don't you need to practice?
直接打嗎 不聯繫一下嗎
(Calling So Min's dad)
- Ji Hyo is doing it. - I rarely call my dad.
是啊
我不常跟爸爸通話
Hello, So Min.
嗯 怎麼了 昭旻
(Playing by ear)
Mom?
媽媽
Yes. Why did you call?
嗯 爲什麼打電話了
(Her mom answered the phone instead of her dad.)
Yes. Why did you call?
嗯 爲什麼打電話了
Mom, where's Dad?
不是 媽 我爸呢
Your dad? Why?
爸爸怎麼了
Well...
沒什麼
Is this a mission?
你這是任務吧
(A mission?)
Is this a mission?
你這是任務吧
(She doesn't know it's not So Min. She just thinks it's a mission.)
Yes, it's a mission. You need to answer my question.
嗯 這是任務
媽 你得答對這個
(You should answer my question.)
No, let your dad do it.
不 讓你爸爸做吧 我不做
(She turns it over to her husband.)
- Hello? - Dad.
喂
- Yes. - Dad, what's my nickname?
爸爸 爸爸 我的暱稱是什麼
- Your nickname? - My nickname.
你的暱稱
我的暱稱 我的暱稱
- You have many. Parrot. - Parrot?
很多啊 鸚鵡
鸚鵡
(He's talking to the fake parrot with no doubt.)
- You have many. Parrot. - Parrot?
很多啊 鸚鵡
鸚鵡
- Why? - Ask him about his blood type.
-問我的血型 血型 血型 -嗯
What's your blood type?
爸爸的血型
Type AB.
AB型
What about me?
我呢 我呢
Yours is also type AB. You take after me.
你也是AB型 因爲隨爸爸啊
- I can't believe this. - What?
這問題太過分了
(So Min's anxious by his conversation with a fake daughter.)
Dad.
爸爸
Who's your favorite member in Running Man?
Running Man裏面最想見的人是
I like Song Ji Hyo.
不管怎麼說 還是想見見宋智孝
-誰 -智孝 智孝
(Song Ji Hyo?)
It's her.
(He likes Ji Hyo, but he doesn't recognize her voice.)
-誰 -智孝 智孝
(The fake mission call continues.)
He doesn't know.
What a coincidence.
已經聽不出來
I think she can talk to him for three hours.
我看能打3個小時
- She can do it for three hours. - You know I like her.
嗯 能打3個小時
(It's way past 3 minutes.)
-這個沒有意義 -已經打開了
All right. It's been nine minutes.
好 成功
(Team Newlyweds fails as it's over 3 minutes.)
Dad, it wasn't me. It was Ji Hyo.
爸 不是我 是智孝姐姐
- Hello, sir. - Dad.
叔叔您好
(So Min's dad finishes his lone mission.)
I guess he wanted to be in our show for a long time.
-爸 -爸爸爲了上節目
- I mean... - He wanted to be on TV.
不是
-想上節目 -想上節目
("Is this a mission" works well.)
- He was so excited to be on TV. - I think...
爲了想上節目
he was too excited to notice her voice.
依我看 爸爸因爲想上節目
(To be on TV, he didn't focus on her voice.)
-沒有注意是誰的聲音 -是啊
- I can't believe this. - I didn't see this coming.
真的是超乎想象 這個
(He did his best to respond to complete the mission.)
If she kept talking, it would last for an hour.
這要是一直說能打一個小時以上
It wasn't me. It was Ji Hyo.
剛纔不是我 是智孝姐姐
I see. She sounded just like you.
聲音一模一樣啊
What?
(He talked to Ji Hyo for a long time whom he wanted to meet.)
- Sir. - I thought it would end right away.
叔叔
- Hello, sir. - How is it possible?
我還以爲馬上就會被發現
叔叔您好
-怎麼會這樣 -您好
That was unbelievable.
絕了
You must be proud of your daughter.
那個 最近昭旻事業順利 很開心吧
I'm always proud of her whether she's successful or not.
沒有 不管順不順利 我女兒都很好
(Touched)
That's so nice.
說得真好
I know. You're so proud of her, but you don't recognize her voice.
是啊 這麼喜歡 爲什麼聽不出聲音呢
I hope we will meet someday. Thank you, sir.
總之我們以後再見 謝謝您
(They could feel the love from the call with So Min's dad.)
- Thank you. Bye. - Thank you.
-是 謝謝您 -謝謝
- Thank you. - Thank you.
-是 謝謝 -謝謝
謝謝
(Other teams are relieved thanks to Ji Hyo.)
That was really good.
不過真的是
- Is it that Ji Hyo did a good job? - I'm disappointed.
我爸爸
這是智孝姐姐模仿得好
不是 我好傷心
(Sad)
- I'm disappointed with Dad. - That was fun.
-我好傷心 -絕了
(Ji Hyo soothes So Min.)
It's important not to get caught at first.
只要過了第一道坎
Then it goes well. Shall we call Sae Ho?
完全不知道
世鎬 給世鎬打一下啊
- Sae Ho? - Let's call Sae Ho. Who'll speak?
-世鎬 給世鎬打一下 -世鎬 世鎬哥哥
(Jae Seok's calling Sae Ho.)
Who wants to try? Who will talk to Sae Ho?
誰來
誰來 哪個隊
- You'll call Sae Ho? - Yes.
-你來打嗎 -嗯
- Hang on. - Or we could try this.
等等 等等 等等 等等
"Hello?" As if he's pulling a joke.
不然乾脆 喂 這樣子
乾脆像開玩笑似的
(Kwang Soo plans to pull a petty trick with his voice.)
- "Hello." - As if he inhaled helium.
喂
-或者像吸了氦氣那樣 -好
- Good idea. - "Hello?"
-喂 -嗯
So who will talk to him?
-誰來做 誰來做 -乾脆
(Kwang Soo will talk to Sae Ho.)
- Kwang Soo, you should try. - Kwang Soo?
-那你來吧 你來 -光洙哥你來吧
-光洙 -嗯
I think he'll notice it right away.
感覺馬上就會聽出來
(Will Sae Ho notice that it's not Jae Seok?)
- I think he will. - I think so.
-嗯 感覺會聽出來 -感覺會聽出來
- We don't know it yet. - It's okay.
-不然把聲音降低 –聲音調最大 調最大
- Hello, Jae Seok. - Where are you, Sae Ho?
喂 哥
你在哪兒呢 世鎬
I'm shooting a TV show now.
啊 我在拍攝呢
(He tries to confuse him with a whispering voice.)
Really? Are you on a break now?
真的嗎 現在在休息嗎
- Pardon? - Can you talk now?
什麼
方便通話嗎
Yes. I can talk now.
是 可以通話
You should go outside now.
你現在到外面接電話
- Okay. - Hurry.
好的
(Sae Ho's manipulated by Kwang Soo's whisper.)
快點快點
- I'm out. - I'm going to...
嗯 出來了 出來了
現在我給你出題 你猜一下
give you a quiz, so you should answer.
- What? - I'm shooting Running Man now.
現在正在拍攝Running Man
Okay.
啊 好的
First, say hello to our viewers.
先向觀衆打聲招呼吧
(He asks Sae Ho to say hello to viewers.)
- To viewers? - Yes. Say hello to them.
給觀衆朋友嗎
嗯 問候一下
Hello, nice to meet you. Thank you so much.
是 非常高興與大家見面 相當感謝
(Sae Ho says what he always says.)
I'm Cho Sae Ho, and I was shooting a TV show.
我是笑星曹世鎬
-現在是拍攝中間休息時間 -不是 小聲點
(Naive Sae Ho completely fell for the voice alteration.)
I'm on a break now.
- I'm glad to talk to... - Lower your voice.
-小聲點 小聲點 -向大家問候了
(Pretending to be in a rush)
- Sae Ho. - Yes?
世鎬 世鎬
Lower your voice.
是
小聲點說 小聲點
Okay. Nice to meet you. Thank you so much.
是 非常高興與大家見面 相當感謝
(Obedient)
Okay. Nice to meet you. Thank you so much.
是 非常高興與大家見面 相當感謝
(Sae Ho says hello as he's ordered.)
I'm Comedian Cho Sae Ho. I'm glad to talk to you.
我是笑星曹世鎬
向大家小心遞上問候
Sae Ho, make an acrostic poem with my name.
世鎬 用劉在錫做三行詩
(Asking for an acrostic poem to kill time)
- What? - An acrostic poem with my name.
-什麼 -用劉在錫做三行詩
- An acrostic poem with your name? - Yes. Yu.
用劉在錫做三行詩嗎
(Out of nowhere)
嗯 劉
Yu.
劉開始了
You are so
(He starts singing right away.)
You are so beautiful
(He sings a serenade of an acrostic poem moanfully.)
Where are you now?
你在哪裏
You should stop him. It's over.
勸一下吧
(Time is up and Jae Seok fails.)
I must say he succeeded.
哥 結束了 哥
-這個吧 哥 -李光洙成功
- Hey, Sae Ho. - Yes.
成功了
喂 鎬世啊 喂 鎬世啊
- How did you not know my voice? - I can't believe this.
是 哥
你怎麼連我的聲音都聽不出來
要瘋了
- It was Kwang Soo. - Hello, I'm Kwang Soo.
剛纔是光洙啊 光洙
你好 我是光洙 哥
That's not it. You suddenly called me. What is going on?
不是 我說突然打來電話
這 這算什麼情況 現在這個
(Sae Ho is blamed even after doing everything he was asked.)
- Do you not know what's going on? - Sae Ho.
喂 不是什麼情況 你
How could you not recognize my voice?
喂 世鎬啊
我的聲音你都不知道嗎
(Other teams are satisfied by Sae Ho's terrible hunch.)
- Well done, Sae Ho. - Good job.
-做得好 世鎬 努力做節目的樣子很帥 -真的
Sae Ho, you weren't so funny today.
啊 鎬世啊 不過今天的口才也不怎麼樣
It's not easy to be funny while getting a perm.
不是 在做燙髮 想口才好不太容易啊
(He still said hello to viewers and made an acrostic poem.)
- Okay. Thank you anyway. - Sae Ho.
-嗯 知道了 謝謝你 鎬世啊 -謝謝
- Have a nice day. - Thank you.
-再見 哥 -嗯 謝謝你
- Sae Ho. - Nice.
-再見 -nice nice
- I'll call you again, Sae Ho. - Good job.
鎬世啊 我回頭再給你打
(Due to Kwang Soo's whisper,)
- Thanks. - So who won?
哥 做得好
-做得好 -這是誰贏啊 這個是誰贏啊
(Jae Seok from Team Human Cultural Asset fails.)
- Who will win this game? - My gosh.
-哎 真是的 -昭旻
- And So Min... - Do you want to call Hyuk?
-我看昭旻 -誰來跟小赫來一下 小赫
(Jong Kook will call Actor Jang Hyuk.)
- Let's call Hyuk. - Do you want to try?
-給小赫打一下 -要試一試嗎
What do you usually say to him?
你平時怎麼通話
I won't tell you.
不告訴你
(Why not?)
Why not? Hey.
-喂 你幹什麼 喂 -在哪呢
You should tell me what to do.
得告訴一下啊
- "What are you doing?" - "What are you doing?"
喂 你幹嘛呢
(Jong Kook tends to talk nonchalantly over the phone.)
- "What's up?" - "What's up? Where are you?"
-你幹嘛呢 -在哪呢
-在幹嘛呢 -幹嘛呢 在哪
- "Hello? Where are you?" - "It's me."
-做得像一點 -喂 在哪呢
"Hey, where are you? Where are you now?"
我在拍攝Running Man呢 你現在
喂 在哪呢 喂 你在哪呢
Don't do that.
你現在
- Don't you sound too sly? - Wait a minute.
你現在說得太卑劣了吧
(Are you saying that's how you will impersonate me?)
- Is that how you think of me? - No, it's not like that.
-等等 你幹嘛學得那麼卑劣 -不是 不是
- No, I don't think he's mean. - How dare you.
(Se Chan is cornered because of the low-quality impersonation.)
Were you imitating Jong Kook?
我沒想那樣的
-你說這是鍾國哥嗎 -居然敢把我
- I was just focusing on your tone. - Okay, try it again.
不是 我只是跟着語調
你怎麼學我的 做一下讓我看看
(He was born to sound vulgar.)
"Hello? Hey, where are you?"
-怎麼做的 -喂
喂 在哪呢
- Aren't you mad, Jong Kook? - "Did you eat?"
-喂 喫飯了嗎 -他一次都沒做過吧
(Jong Kook's angry to hear his vulgar tone.)
Do I sound that vulgar?
-我是小滑頭嗎 -不是
- No, it wasn't vulgar. - What?
- Se Chan, you try calling Hyuk. - All right.
-世燦來跟小赫通電話吧 -好
(Se Chan will try calling Jang Hyuk.)
- "Hello?" - I think you can fake his voice.
-喂 -感覺你能做得很像
Here's the ring tone.
-在哪呢 -嗯 可以了 打過去了
(Calling him)
Put it on speakerphone.
-免提 免提 -喂
Look at it shaking.
-免提 -聲音很大
Hey, Jong Kook.
嗯 鍾國
Hyuk, where are you?
嗯 小赫 你在哪
Me?
我啊 我現在在奧林匹克大道上
I'm on Olympic Boulevard Expressway right now.
Where are you headed?
去哪兒啊
(He naturally finds out where he is.)
I just dropped the kid off.
先送孩子再回趟家 還得去趟江陵
I need to go home first then I have to go to Gangneung.
So you're going to Gangneung?
去江陵啊
Yes.
嗯嗯
Have you eaten?
飯呢
(Not doubting at all)
I will on my way to Gangneung.
得在路上喫
You will on the way?
啊 在路上喫啊
- Yes. - Gosh.
-嗯嗯嗯嗯 -哎喲
(Presenting a topic)
I'm on Jeju Island. The weather is great here.
喂 我來了濟州島 天氣可好了
You're in Jeju Island?
你去濟州島了
Yes, I finished filming. The weather is so good.
嗯 拍攝結束了 天氣挺好的
Hey, doesn't Tae Hyun call you these days?
喂 你最近沒有接到太鉉的電話嗎
Gosh, he keeps calling me. I'm going out of my mind.
喂 我都受不了了 一直給我打電話
(The subject changes.)
哎 真是的
(He starts having small talk.)
Why is he talking so much?
-喂 –怎麼會聊到這裏
Why does he call me whenever he's drunk?
喂 太鉉怎麼總喝醉了給我打電話啊
That's what he does these days.
他最近
(He starts to spin a yarn.)
I think he's obsessed with it.
有點對你產生了勝負心
(Summary: "He keeps calling you because you're not picking up.")
Because I'm not answering his calls.
-這小子怎麼不接電話 -是嗎
Is that right?
(Se Chan makes a few rejoinders,)
It's just making me go crazy.
啊 要瘋了 要瘋了
I was dragged by him a couple of times though.
我也被拉去過一次
(and Hyuk starts talking.)
(Sloppy response)
- Gosh, he dragged you? - He sure did.
被拉過去了啊
Hyuk, where are you?
小赫 你在哪兒
- Who is this? - "Who is this?"
額 這又是誰
Hyuk, where are you?
這又是誰
小赫 你在哪兒
(There's no way they're going to complete the mission anyway.)
(Where's Jong Kook?)
Who is this?
是誰啊
I'm Jae Seok.
我是在錫
(Jong Kook fails his mission.)
- He didn't know it was me. - Hey.
-完全不知道 -喂 你這傢伙
- He really didn't know. - Gosh, Hyuk.
-哇 居然不知道 -不是 小赫
- Even when I talked in my tone. - I can't believe it.
這個 我用自己聲音說的
(Hyuk completely believed the crappy impersonation.)
- He really didn't know. - Hyuk.
他真的是被騙過去了
- It's so funny. - Yes.
太搞笑了
(Hyuk.)
You've been talking to Se Chan.
你剛纔一直在跟世燦通話
There's no way he sounded like Jong Kook.
不是 這哪裏像鍾國哥了
(He's really naive without prejudice or doubt.)
I talked in my own tone.
我用自己聲音說的
- A voice he's never heard before. - Hyuk.
-不是 喂 小赫 -陌生的聲音
- Hyuk. - It's hilarious.
-小赫 -絕了
- Yes. - How can he not know?
-嗯 -怎麼會不知道呢
How can you not know it's someone else?
你怎麼就聽不出聲音呢
(He still thinks it's Jong Kook.)
So who was I talking to?
等等 我跟誰通話的
- You were talking to Se Chan. - I think he thinks you're me.
你跟世燦通話的
(He thinks...)
他以爲你是我呢 現在
And you're talking to Jae Seok right now.
喂 我是在錫哥
Hyuk, please get it together!
哥 你打起精神啊
(Hyuk is still in confusion.)
- Hyuk! - Hyuk!
-小赫哥 -小赫哥
(Laughing)
小赫 你怎麼就不知道鍾國的聲音呢
Hyuk.
How can you not recognize Jong Kook's voice?
The truth is we're not that close.
-我們不怎麼親 -什麼
(He forces an excuse as he feels embarrassed.)
What?
- Hey, you ruined my mission. - I did?
喂 因爲你失敗了 現在
It's not you, is it?
你現在不是你吧
It is me!
是我
(He's all confused now and still can't recognize his voice.)
It's me, you fool!
是我啊 小子
He can't trust anyone now.
現在懷疑了 不信了
Hyuk, you're so funny.
小赫太搞笑了
(Though he can't recognize the voice, they're still good friends.)
- Thanks. I'll talk to you soon. - Thank you, Hyuk.
小赫 謝謝了 我們回頭
- All right. Bye. - Thank you!
小赫 謝謝你
嗯 知道了
謝謝
Take care of yourself.
-小赫 謝謝你 -小赫 謝謝你
-祝你健康 -嗯
(Jong Kook fails his mission as Se Chan talked to Hyuk instead.)
I can't believe him.
小赫怎麼會
- This is so funny. - He talked so smoothly.
口若懸河 口若懸河
It's so easy to fool him.
他很容易騙啊
Se Chan, call someone you know.
世燦也打一下吧
(Se Chan of Team Newlyweds will try calling his celebrity friend.)
Yes, you should pick one of your friends too
是啊 你也得打一個
Who should I call?
給誰打呢
(The comedian)
How about calling Jae Joon?
給在俊打一下啊 在俊
- Kang Jae Joon? - Yes.
-姜在俊哥嗎 -嗯
- Jae Joon will notice it's not me. - All right.
在俊哥的話肯定會被發現
(Se Chan will call Jae Joon.)
在俊
- Why don't Jong Kook call him? - What do you usually call him?
鍾國哥來說 怎麼樣
(How does Se Chan speak when he's on the phone with Jae Joon?)
你平時怎麼叫在俊
- Do you speak casually with him? - No, I speak formally.
說平語嗎
-不 說敬語 -怎麼稱呼
(First...)
- "Hello, sir?" Like this? - As soon as he answers...
-不是 一接電話就 -這樣的話
he says, "My goodness."
哎喲 這麼起頭
- "My goodness." - "My goodness."
-哎喲 -哎喲
- "Where are you?" - "Where are you?"
您在哪呢
(Se Chan likes to drag the politest expression.)
- "I'm off work now." - "My goodness."
-是 我剛剛結束 -哎喲
- "I'm off work now." - "Where are you?"
-我剛剛結束 -您在哪呢
Jong Kook, sounds like him.
鍾國哥很像
(Like this?)
- "Jong Kook." - Oh, that's it.
鍾國啊
- You're good. - That's good.
-鍾國啊 哥做得很像 -很好 很好 很好
(Jong Kook will talk to Jae Joon as he sounds similar.)
Then you should try calling him.
哥 你來給在俊打一下
- Yes, you try it. - Yes.
-你試試 -嗯
It's on speaker.
哪個是免提
- My goodness. - My goodness.
-哎喲 -哎喲
- Where are you? - Where are you?
您在哪呢
(It's a smooth start.)
Are you home?
安全到達了嗎
I'm somewhere I don't want to be.
我來了不想來的地方
Oh, gosh.
哎喲 是在家裏嗎
You mean you're home?
I'm at the office of Comedy Big League.
是喜聯辦公室
I see.
哎呦喂
- Wait a minute. - I...
-真是 -等等
- Your voice is... Is this Se Chan? - My gosh.
-現在聲音是梁世燦嗎 -這
(The original "My goodness")
- My goodness. - My goodness.
-哎喲 -哎喲
(Jae Joon noticed it in 15 seconds.)
- It wasn't Se Chan. - It wasn't him.
-不是的 -被發現了
- It's me. I'm Jong Kook. - Hey.
是哥 我是鍾國哥 在俊
- Jong Kook, how have you been? - Good.
鍾國哥 你好
We're on a mission right now.
嗯 我們在做任務呢
(He explains to Jae Joon that it was a mission.)
Jae Joon, you recognized it too fast so our mission is ruined.
-在俊啊 -嗯
你發現得太快 失敗了
(Put me on.)
I'll let you talk to Se Chan. Just a minute.
喂 我把電話給世燦 世燦 等一下
- All right. - Bye.
-嗯 -嗯
My goodness.
哎喲
Wait. This isn't him either.
哎喲 等等 這也不是啊
(It's not so easy to fool him.)
- He noticed again. - It's so hard to fool him.
不是 不是
- My goodness. - My goodness.
-很難 很難 -哎喲
Hey, it's me. It's Se Chan.
哥 是我 我 我 是世燦
Stop lying to me!
不要說謊
No, it's really is me!
是我啊 哥 是我
(Still doubting)
- Come on. It's me! - He doesn't...
哥 是我
(After the brief call with Jae Joon,)
- It's me! - recognize the real one either.
-他 他根本不知道 -哥 是我
- Jae Joon. - He's suspicious of everyone.
在俊啊
-他疑心很重啊 -他就是
(So Min called Ji Hyo's brother to play Word Chain.)
Pottery.
陶瓷
Greasing.
上油
How can her family member not notice her voice?
爲什麼家人們都察覺不出來
(Ji Hyo's brother didn't recognize it for a while.)
- I'll talk to you later. - Thank you, Sung Moon.
知道了成文
謝謝你 成文
- Here's the result of the mission. - Okay.
-所以任務的結果是 -是
Se Chan and So Min's team completed the mission in 15 seconds.
是
只有世燦 昭旻一隊在15秒內成功
(Only Team Newlyweds succeeded once in 15 seconds.)
But the others failed.
其餘的隊伍都失敗了
One more team can join them.
-是 -真的嗎
所以只有一隊能下車
(They can choose a team to go on the course.)
So pick one team to take them with you.
-選另外一對一起出去吧 -這樣也挺好
This is good.
We won so we don't have to pay for it though, right?
-反正我們出去的話 我們不用花錢吧 -是
(They're saving money as they're both getting off.)
- Yes, you can save your money. - That's right.
-是 省下錢了 -是啊
Then you should take...
那不如帶走這兩位乞丐吧
these penniless guys with you.
- Yes, the old guys. - These guys?
-老人家們 -他們嗎
(Giving the chance to the ones that came to Jeju with 7 dollars)
Yes, we should take the old guys with us.
是 老人家們
帶上老人家們吧
- Take pity on them. - Yes, take them.
-不如 -怎麼能說是乞丐呢
(Team Newlyweds and Team Human Cultural Asset...)
- Yes, take us. - All right.
還不如
-是啊 帶上我們吧 -是啊
(will go on the Photo of a Lifetime Course.)
OK
All right then.
-好 被選拔的人們可以下車了 -是
(They'll go to take photos of their lifetime near the shore.)
- Chosen members should get off. - All right.
- It's pretty. - Wear your masks.
真漂亮
口罩 口罩 得帶上口罩
All right.
是 哥
(The photo spot of Jeju with the entrancing sunset)
- The four can get off the bus. - All right.
-請四位下車 -好
Have fun, guys.
好
請慢走
We'll go take some pictures.
好 我們去拍點照片了
- See you. - This is so nice.
-慢走 -哎呦 真棒
So Min, it's this way.
昭旻 是這邊
(The newlyweds are excited to see such beautiful scenery.)
Gosh, this is nice.
-哇 真棒 -喂
(With the sunset painting the sea red in the background...)
- It's amazing. - It's so pretty.
-真不錯 -太漂亮了
I think it's this spot. Photo of A Lifetime Course.
好像就是這裏 人生美照
(and cute little chairs lined up)
- Where? - There.
-在哪 -這裏
Yes, this is it.
哇 這裏這裏
(Any photo will turn into a photo of a lifetime here.)
- There's something to eat too. - We should take photos here.
-還有喫的 -還有喫的
就是這 在這拍就行
(There are also things to enjoy.)
Gosh, that's tangerine juice.
哇 那還有橘子果汁
It's really delicious.
這個很好喫 這個很好喫
(And a Polaroid camera)
There's a Polaroid camera too.
還有拍立得相機
Gosh, what's this?
哇 這都是什麼
(There are different props prepared.)
You may choose the services. The prices are listed on the menu.
就按這個價格購買商品就行
(Childlike innocence)
So Min, you can buy that. But come here first.
昭旻先買這個 你過來
It's tangerine bread, isn't it?
原來是橘子麪包
- Let's buy the couples' bracelets. - Okay.
這個 我們買這個手鍊吧
好的
(The newlyweds get couple's bracelets.)
- Choose one. - Okay. It's pretty.
-一人戴一個 -嗯 很好 好好看
It costs 30 dollars.
手鍊30000韓元
I'll take two for me and my wife.
我和我妻子來個這個
(Seok Sam also buys a present for his wife.)
You said you're not married.
你不是說你沒結婚嗎
- I have a wife. - Now he was a wife.
哎呦 還有
這個 這個
(Jae Seok buys postcards for his children.)
I'll buy these for Ji Hyo and Na Eun.
-OK -我要送給志浩和娜恩
- Then take two. Three? - I will buy...
那就兩個 三個
(The highest price on the menu is 50 dollars.)
photo of your lifetime taken by Chan Hee. It’s 50 dollars.
燦熙哥給拍的人生美照50000韓元
That's good.
啊 不錯
We will take the immortal photo of...
-我們要不朽的燦熙給拍的人生美照 -現場照
- The Polaroid camera. - your lifetime taken by Chan Hee.
("Immortal Chan Hee" is...)
- Yes, I'd like that. - I want photos from Chan Hee.
-我也要燦熙導演 -燦熙導演給拍的人生美照
(Kang Chan Hee the cameraman with years of experience...)
(who has worked...)
(for numerous other shows.)
(The living legend will take their photos.)
- Yes, Chan Hee will take photos. - Okay.
我們也來個燦熙哥給拍的
是
Here we go.
要來效果了
Shouldn't the apprentice be stand up?
弟子 你站着會不會好點
(A human cultural asset and a teacher who is strict)
Gosh, sit here then.
-哎呦 怎麼還 坐這吧 -你先站着
Shouldn't the apprentice be standing up?
(If only he wasn't my teacher...)
- I'll hold up the reflector. - Okay.
我來舉反射板
是 是
What's with these two shots?
這個同框 這個同框是什麼
Smile at least.
哥 你能不能笑一下
(The serious and strict teacher and the old pupil)
What is this?
這算什麼
(So Min in charge of bubbles)
Is it done?
行了嗎
1, 2, 3.
1 2 3
(Click)
(Teacher.)
- You take one alone. - All right.
-拍個獨照吧 -好的 好的
(Random words)
- You need one for your funeral. - For his funeral?
還得準備一張遺照
(The pupil looks for a chance to get rid of his teacher.)
遺照
- Here it is. - Yes.
出來了
(What will the photos by "Immortal Chan Hee" look like?)
I wonder how it came out. I wish my bubbles are in it.
-看看 -希望拍到了肥皂泡
Here.
來
(What's wrong?)
This looks like...
兩個人馬上
they're going to die soon.
-這是什麼 -像是這個世界馬上就要完蛋一樣
("Ascension" by Kang Chan Hee)
Is it a photo of their spirits?
靈魂照
- Are we ghosts? - Why did it come out like this?
是逆光了
太過分了
(What is this?)
It looks like we're going to die soon.
-太過分了 - 馬上要離開人世的感覺
(It's quite low in quality for a 50-dollar service.)
- And it costs 50 dollars? - Gosh.
這就是50000韓元的照片嗎
Gosh, Chan Hee.
我說燦熙哥
- Immortal photo? - Where's your immortal photo?
-不朽的燦熙哥 -不朽的燦熙哥
(Restless)
What is this?
這簡直是 拍得跟要馬上要昇天的人一樣
How can you make us look like we're about to die?
(The customer explodes after seeing a psychic photo.)
Let me see it.
這怎麼行
我看看 我看看
(Kang Chan Hee, cameraman, specializing in videos)
Gosh, this makes me sad.
這個真的好傷心
(The newlweds)
- You two get a photo. - Yes, we should.
-你們也拍一下 -我們也得拍一張
(Next are the newlyweds.)
- Hold up the reflector. - All right. The reflector.
麻煩舉一下反射板
- Blow some bubbles too. - Okay.
-反射板 -也來點肥皂泡
Blow some bubbles, please.
是
麻煩來點肥皂泡
Hey, Mr. Human Cultural Asset.
非物質文化遺產先生
- Help us out. - All right.
我來給你做
(A generous human cultural asset)
(Take this.)
- Seok Sam. - Yes, sir.
-那個 石三 -是
(He's strict only toward his pupil.)
"Seok Sam."
石三
(The human reflector is docile.)
- "Hold this up." - Okay.
-來 -舉好了
Here we go.
來
("Immortal Chan Hee" helps them with the pose.)
Se Chan, move towards So Min.
世燦再往昭旻這靠點
- Okay. - Look towards her.
-這樣嗎 -視線轉到她這邊
(Turning)
Look towards her.
視線 視線
(Flustered)
Wait a minute.
這個就有點 等一下
-視線 -這個就有點 等一下
(His face got as red as his gums.)
Wait a minute.
Just do it.
趕緊的吧
Can't you take off your sunglasses?
能不能脫掉墨鏡
(He can't even look her in the eye.)
- That looks nice. - Gosh, the bubbles.
-可以了嗎 -這肥皂泡
1, 2...
1 2
- Wait. - Do you usually press on two?
-在喊2的時候拍嗎 -等一下
1, 2.
1 2
(Clicking on two)
- Wait. - Do you usually press on two?
-在喊2的時候拍嗎 -等一下
- Do you usually do that? - You should press on three.
本來就這樣嗎
我說哥 怎麼不是在3的時候拍
(Nervous)
Is it normal to go on two?
而是在2的時候拍
本來就是在2拍嗎
Again.
-不小心按到了 -再來
(He tries again.)
- Here we go. - Seok Jin, you're too close.
-來 開 -石鎮 你靠得太近了
(Get out of the angle.)
- I am? - Get out of the way.
-啊 是 -哥 你走開
- Seok Jin, you're too close. - Okay.
石鎮 你靠得太近了
-啊 是 -哥 你走開
(The human reflector tried to get in the shot.)
Only two of us should be in the picture.
-哥 這是我們兩個人拍的 -哥
Seok Jin.
(They try again without the unwelcome guest.)
- Here we go. - Ready.
開始了
1, 2, 3.
來 1 2 3
(Clicking)
- This one will be good. - Great.
哇 這次很不錯
(It was taken well this time.)
- I'm sure of it. - Yes, I'm sure.
-很棒 -這個肯定拍得好
出來了
- So Min. - Yes?
-可是昭旻 -怎麼了
I think you're really enjoying this.
-不是開玩笑 我看你是真的很開心 -很開心
(Look at this.)
This is too...
哥哥
- Let me see. - Look at the photo.
-我看看 -看照片
- What is this? - What's this?
喂 這算什麼
這算什麼
This looks really weird. What do I do?
這張照片太奇怪了 怎麼辦
(It looks like an actual honeymoon photo.)
It's weird.
這個就有點
We look too close.
拍得很厲害了
(Seok Sam gets excited.)
- It's like you're really on a trip. - Yes, this looks real.
這個是真的旅行照
(Embarrassed)
- Come on. This isn't right. - You two look real.
換掉吧
-真的 -我覺得這個不行
- Looks like you're really in love. - Yes, they're in love.
-這可是因爲真愛才拍出來的 -這可是真愛
(The couple's photo crosses the line between role-playing and reality.)
You two look like a couple on a honeymoon trip.
真的很像 度蜜月 來度蜜月的情侶
And you took a photo of us looking like we're about to die?
喂 哥  就拍我們拍得跟下地獄的人一樣
(Enraged again)
("The Boatmen of Jordan River" by Kang Chan Hee)
- Come on. - What's with our photo?
-我說 -這是什麼
How can you make it look like it's the end of our world?
拍成世界末日的感覺 這樣也行嗎
(Complaining)
- Their picture is so much nicer. - What about our photo?
-給他們拍成這樣 哥 -這算什麼
- Thank you. - Thank you.
-謝謝 -謝謝
(Sorry.)
- This photo's so funny. - The photo is...
這個太搞笑了
(They wasted 250 dollars because of "Immortal Chan Hee".)
-拍成這樣很像 -喂 我們
We spent 250 dollars on photos.
-光是拍照花了25萬韓元 -我們花了多少
(While the four members are spending a lot of money,)
- How much did we spend? - We can...
-啊 可是還能花 點 還能花點 -什麼
- How much? - We can spend more.
(the rest of the members are somewhere they can't see the ocean.)
Everyone, please get off.
成員們 請下車
(One of them will have to pay without even watching the ocean.)
Four of you can't take photos here.
好 到這也拍不了照的4位
But one of you will have to pay for the photos.
四位中的一位還要支付
(Photo of a Lifetime Course)
You'll play Tumbling Tug-of-War to decide who will pay.
選拔支付人的遊戲是蠕動的拔河
(Waving Tug of War)
- Tug-of-war? - Tug-of-war?
-拔河嗎 -拔河嗎
(It's a 1-on-1 tournament.)
It's a one on one tournament.
會以1對1 淘汰賽的方式進行
Two members will wear...
參加對決的二人穿戴用彈簧連接的腰帶
(2 players will wear a belt connected by a string.)
belts attached at each end of the spring.
(Within 1 minute, they must send...)
You have one minute...
在1分鐘的限制時間內
to make the CD in the middle move towards your opponent.
要把中間的CD儘快送到對方那裏纔行
(the CD across without using their hands.)
- Towards your opponent's side? - Yes.
-啊 是送到對方那嗎 -是
(The loser's team will pay for the expenses.)
You lose if the CD is close to you.
因此靠得更近的這邊是輸家
The one who loses until the end...
到最後決賽後後最後一名要支付所有的費用
(Send the CD away to avoid paying.)
will pay for the photos.
So the CD should be far away from me?
-只要是這個CD比我遠就行了吧 -是的
- That's right. - Okay.
okok
(Kwang Soo, Haha, Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo)
Let's start with Lee Kwang Soo and Haha.
-那麼從李光洙和HAHA開始 -好
(Round 1, Kwang Soo versus Haha)
- Ready. - How do I do this?
-準備 開始 -到黑色的話
(Nervous)
- The black mark is the middle. - Set.
(The game starts.)
Haha, you're doing great.
做得好 做得好
(The CD moves toward Kwang Soo as soon as the game begins.)
That's it! Great!
我們HAHA做得好 做得好 做得好
(Fancy hip movements)
Haha, you're doing great.
做得好 我們HAHA做得好 做得好 做得好
(The CD won't seem to leave Kwang Soo.)
Okay! That's great.
OK 很好 很好 很好 很好
You're doing great.
(The Math prodigy learned how to play games from a book.)
You're doing great. Great!
(This is fun.)
Haha, you're doing great.
-很好 很好 -光洙
Gosh, Kwang Soo!
Great. Swing it more.
做得好 要那樣做
(This won't do.)
Great!
做得好
(Doing the nasty hip dance)
You're doing great!
做得好 做得好 做得好
(With his vulgar hip movements,)
Here he goes. Great.
很好 HAHA很好
(he succeeds in pushing the CD away.)
No, you can't let him win.
不行 不行 不能那樣 OK
Okay. There you go.
(The Pythagorean pelvis that makes use of the x-axis and y-axis)
You can't use your wrists like that.
是不是一直在用手腕啊
Okay. Again.
OK 再來
- No. - You can do this.
-5 -不行
(Use your energy, Assistant Manager Haha.)
We need to go!
可以做到的
-4 -要弄過去 要再弄過去 要弄過去
(Will Kwang Soo win like this?)
- We need to go! - 3, 2...
-4 -要弄過去 要再弄過去 要弄過去
-3 2 - 要弄過去 要弄過去
(Game over)
(The whistle was blown.)
(Centerline)
- What is happening? - We win!
-嗯 幹嘛回來 - 好了
Hey!
(The CD moved toward Kwang Soo beyond the centerline.)
- What is happening? - We win!
-嗯 幹嘛回來 到最後 - 好了
- What? Why is it coming toward me? - We win!
(Assistant Manager Haha won after an unexpected buzzer-beater.)
- It passed the centerline. - But this is...
超過了 超過了
(How could this happen?)
- The finishing point matters. - Yes.
最後過了中線停止了
(As a runner-up at the Olympiad, he lacks persistence.)
- Kwang Soo. - Gosh.
-光洙 -好笑
- Gosh, this is... - This is so funny.
太好笑了
- This is so funny. - Why am I dizzy?
-我怎麼這麼暈 -太好笑了
(Round 2, Jong Kook versus Ji Hyo)
- Should I go? - Ji Hyo, you must win.
姐姐一定要贏
(If Jong Kook wins, Team Olympiad has to pay.)
This is amazing, Jong Kook. We just have to win this round.
試試吧 哥 贏這次就行
- Let's do this. - Okay.
-OK OK - OK
It's over for us if you lose this round, Ji Hyo.
-姐姐 這次輸的話就結束了 -贏吧
Let's win.
(The game on the edge of a cliff...)
- Ready. - Move your hand away from it.
-準備 - 把手拿開
(starts.)
We must win.
一定要贏 一定要贏
(The CD moves toward Ji Hyo as soon as it begins.)
- Do it the other way. - That's it.
-好了 好了 -反過來 反過來
Do it the other way.
反過來
- Ji Hyo. - Gosh.
- Jong Kook. - Do it the other way.
-反過來 -哥 一開始
(He's clenching his molars hard.)
Jong Kook, don't use your strength too much from the beginning.
哥 一開始就不要用力 哥
(He ignores her and moves forward.)
- Ji Hyo, you're doing a good job. - What!
-姐姐 轉吧 姐姐 轉吧 -啊 爲什麼別過來
- Don't come toward me! - Ji Hyo!
(You're scaring me.)
-轉吧 -啊 爲什麼別過來 別過來 別共來
(Ji Hyo retreats and looks for a chance.)
- Don't come toward me! - Go the other way! You got this!
-反過來 反過來 - 很好 很好
No.
-別過來 -不對 反過來 反過來
(New Recruit Kim only moves forward.)
- Don't come toward me. - The other way!
That's right.
對 對
(Neck-and-neck)
End it now.
現在要弄了 現在要弄了
Ji Hyo, endure it.
姐姐堅持住 堅持住
(Moving forward for the 2nd time)
Endure it. You're winning right now!
-堅持住 -做的好
- Don't come toward me. - You can do it!
姐姐 現在在贏呢
-不要過來 -可以的
(What's wrong with him?)
Don't come toward me!
做的好
-不要過來 - 可以的
- Ji Hyo. - Endure it until we win.
做的好
(If Ji Hyo loses, Team Olympiad has to pay.)
-堅持 -在贏呢 拜託
Please...
Four...
-43 -姐姐 不要放棄
- 3, 2. - Ji Hyo, don't give up.
That's it!
-21 -好了
(Game over)
(The recruit who kept pushing won.)
Why did you keep coming at me?
-幹嘛一直過來 -OK
- Okay! - Okay!
我很怕
(Running Trading Company is exempted from paying.)
That's it.
好了
- New Recruit Kim! - He did it on purpose.
-金社員 -故意的
Our company's name is actually "New Recruit".
其實我們公司名字叫新職員
(Team Olympiad will have to pay.)
Team Olympiad lost.
-奧林匹克競賽隊失敗 要結算 -OK
You will have to pay for everything.
- Okay. - We're going to win.
-這樣下去會拿第一呢 -拿第一吧
- We might come in first. - I know.
(It would cost a lot.)
I think it will cost a lot of money.
-應該花很多錢了吧 -是啊
- We lost. - That's right.
We will take everything like family and group photos.
團體照 全家福什麼都要拍啊
(They spent money for no reason without even seeing the sea.)
- Come here, let's take a photo. - Okay.
-東勳 過來 我們在這裏拍照吧 - OK
(They're posing like partners.)
(Ji Hyo also joined the selfie.)
Come here.
過來吧
Kwang Soo.
光洙哥不拍嗎
Aren't you going to join them?
- Let Lee Kwang Soo in the photo. - Let's go.
李光洙也加入吧
(Ignoring)
Let's go.
-走吧 - 走吧
We're done. We're done taking photos.
結束了 都拍完了
- Let's go. - We're done.
-走吧 -結束了 都拍完了
We're done taking photos.
(Even his teammate abandoned him.)
We took a lovely photo.
-照了漂亮的照片 -都拍完了
- The sky is lovely. - Hurry up.
所以快點過來
- There's no airplane passing by? - No.
飛機不來嗎
Kwang Soo, hurry up and leave.
光洙 快點 快點過來
(He just spits out harsh words.)
(They heard everything.)
An airplane passed by.
飛機 飛機過去了
- It was an airplane. - Where?
-飛機 - 哪裏 哪裏
- There's an airplane over there. - Kwang Soo.
-那邊的飛機 -飛機早就飛過去了
It already passed by far away.
(The course ended by just leaving several wounds on Kwang Soo.)
(They completed the course.)
- Okay. - Please get in the car.
-辛苦了 -這個太搞笑了
- This is so funny. - That's right.
(The 4 returned after enjoying.)
- Did you take photos? - It's so funny. What should I do?
-拍得怎麼樣 -照片太搞笑了怎麼辦 看看這個
- Take a look. - You should try one of these.
喫一下這個吧 這個 這個
- This is so... - But you look really...
哇 這個拍得太和諧了
(Newlywed couple)
- close and lovely in the photo. - Who wants some tangerine juice?
(They check out the photos.)
-誰想喝飲料 -我喝
- Me. - I want some.
(Meanwhile, Se Chan smiles as he looks at the photos.)
- Try this. - This is funny. "Newlyweds."
嚐嚐這個
-這很搞笑呢 新婚夫婦 -我們要出發了
We'll get going now.
This is really good.
-哇 這個真的很好喫 -你給他好看的照片呢
(Assistant Manager Ha loves make-believe relationships.)
- It looks good. - You gave him the good picture.
(The newlywed couple makes Assistant Manager Ha smile.)
- The total fee we used is... - Yes?
這次花費總額之後結算
We spent a lot.
You became sentimental.
感性
Take a look at that.
咿呀 看這個 看這個
(Jeju's sunset induces exclamation.)
Look at the horizon.
看看海平面 海平面
Look at the sunset.
哇 看看那天空和晚霞
(While everyone is immersed in the scenery,)
Look.
-咿呀 看這個 看這個 -看海平面 看海平面
(Seok Jin is stealing snacks.)
(Gosh, Seok Jin.)
Look at the horizon.
(The pupil is not romantic since he's worn out from the hardships.)
The sky is really beautiful.
天空真的好美啊
We're on our way to eat something good.
-我們要去喫好喫的了 -啊 是嗎
- Really? You should eat this. - Yes.
-是的 -你喫吧
This time...
-這次 -啊 真是的
(He returns the snack right away.)
- You should eat this. - Yes.
-是的 -你喫吧
-這次 -啊 真是的
(He can't believe it.)
- Seok Jin... - Are you serious?
-不不 哥 -真的太糟糕了
(Seok Sam threw the snack to his teacher to have delicacy.)
- His tone was... - "You should eat this."
so detestable.
-你喫吧 -語調本身就很討人厭
It's obvious that he was serious.
-但是這是真心的 -但是這個
But he's...
(Shocked)
- being serious. - I was joking.
-這是真心的 真心 -開玩笑的
(Seok Sam's too honest.)
- Were you joking? - You were serious.
-開玩笑的 -不是爲了搞笑嗎
- He wasn't trying to be funny. - "You should eat this."
- "You should eat this." - He's serious.
你你你 你喫吧
He's being real.
(Embarrassed)
I'm dumbfounded by the timing I said that.
說話的時機真是絕了
(Sulking)
I'm sorry.
-對不起 -你你你 你喫吧
"You should eat this."
(A restaurant in Jeju)
- Look at this view. - Gosh,
-哇 看這裏的風景 -看景色 太美了
look at this panorama. It's so nice.
(They're excited...)
Since the sun is setting, it's making me slightly sentimental.
-因爲晚霞 心變得暖暖的  -對啊 心裏變得
(to enjoy the meal with the sunset on the horizon.)
- Yes, my heart is... - Do you know that?
- This is the third schedule. - Yes.
-各位 這是第三個行程 -好的
(The third schedule in the tour package)
We will enjoy playing Jeju Island Full Course Feast...
以開闊的海景爲背景享受濟州島晚餐
(Jeju Island Full Course Feast...)
(with the clear ocean view as the background)
with a clear ocean view as the background.
Braised hairtail, which is a dish that represents Jeju Island,
準備了代表濟州島的燉帶魚和
(Braised hairtail, which is a dish that represents Jeju Island,)
(and all kinds of fresh seafood will be served.)
and all kinds of fresh seafood have been prepared.
-各種新鮮的海鮮 -我要喫
I'm going to eat this.
The number of people who will enjoy the feast is five people.
-能享用晚餐的人員只有5人 -喫吧
(Only 5 people can enjoy the feast.)
- Let's eat. - The number is too little.
但是T.O.太少了
(5 out of 8...)
- Five people... - That's a lot.
8個人當中5個人的話算很多了
(is not bad.)
It's out of eight people.
(Enthusiastic)
- Five people are doable. - Yes, it is.
-5個人可以試一試 -可以試一試
This game is Half Proverb Quiz.
這次遊戲是一半諺語問答
(Package Option Trip Race, third mission)
(Half Proverb Quiz)
It will be an individual match.
以個人戰進行
- It's not a team match. - We shouldn't do proverbs.
-諺語 -啊 這不是團隊戰啊
It's advantageous to Team Olympiad.
不要那種諺語呢
這對奧林匹克競賽隊太有利了
(Team Olympiad looks worried.)
That's possible.
-也可以那麼說 -就是說
- That's right. - Proverbs are...
Five questions will be given to each person continuously.
諺語的話
給每人連續出5道題
(5 questions will be given to each person continuously.)
Listen to the last part of the sentence...
-聽完我們提的諺語後 -OK
(Listen to the last part of the proverb...)
- of the proverb we say. - Okay.
(and complete the front part within 3 seconds.)
Complete the front part within three seconds.
-出門那天 -3秒內要完成前半句
- That's hard. - Proverbs.
-啊 好難 好難 - 好難
(They have to answer the front part.)
- You'll tell us the last part only? - Only the last part?
不是 等一下 不說前半句的
If we say the last part, you have the get the first part.
-而是說後半句的嗎 -只有後半句
-說後半句 答對前半句就行 -前半句
- The front part? - There are a lot of hard proverbs.
有很多難懂的諺語
(The game order)
- We will start right away. - Okay.
-那麼馬上開始吧 - 好的
(The game order)
- Let's start with this side. - Let's start with this side.
-從這邊開始吧 - 從這邊開始吧
(If you can't answer in 3 seconds, you fail.)
If you can't say it after we say "1, 2, 3.",
說完123之內沒說出來就算答錯了
- you will be out. - Okay.
(Ji Hyo will try first.)
Ready,
-OK -好的
準備開始
go!
It's better to get beaten...
-不如捱打 -2 3
1, 2, 3.
It's better to get beaten...
-不如捱打 -2 3
(Timeout)
Okay.
OK OK
- "It's better to get beaten"? - "It's better to get beaten"?
-不如捱打 -不如捱打是什麼來着
(What's "It's better to get beaten"?)
It's better to get beaten first.
既然要捱打 晚挨不如早挨
- "It's better to get beaten first." - I couldn't think of it.
捱打 捱打
(It's confusing.)
This is confusing though.
-啊 這容易混淆 -這個不太清楚
- I'm not sure about this. - This is hard.
-好難 -不如捱打 不太清楚
- It's better to get beaten... - This is the second question.
第二道題 是小菜（餓了喫糠甜如蜜）
"The best side dish..."
1, 2, 3.
1 2 3
- Quail eggs! - Hunger!
-鵪鶉蛋 -市場
-不是鵪鶉蛋 -是市場
- "Quail eggs"? - What do you mean by "quail eggs"?
鵪鶉蛋 鵪鶉蛋是什麼
(The best side dish is quail eggs?)
- Is it "quail eggs"? - It was "Hunger."
-說是鵪鶉蛋 - 鵪鶉蛋
-啊 市場 -鵪鶉蛋
(Quail eggs are the best side dish.)
- Quail eggs... - Quail eggs are also a side dish.
對呢 鵪鶉蛋是小菜呢
(When you think about it, it's not exactly wrong.)
Quail eggs are a side dish.
鵪鶉蛋是小菜
- Please give us a little more. - This is hard.
再多給一點句子吧 再多給一點
(The Olympiad winner isn't good at anything aside from math.)
It's too far back.
好難
太后面了
- This is the third question. - Okay.
Ok
This is hard though.
真的太難了
Spraying ashes on...
垂成
Cooked rice.
功敗
(The members figured out the answer right away.)
Spraying ashes on...
垂成
(What about Ji Hyo?)
Spraying ashes on...
(Timeout)
- Spraying ashes on cooked rice. - No way.
功敗垂成
晚了 晚了
(It was close, but she failed.)
She said it too late.
晚了 晚了
How could we not answer even one question?
一道題都答不對 一道題都
(Feeling confident)
But I think this is doable.
但是如果是這種程度我能行
- Okay. - We got zero points.
Ok
(Ji Hyo got 0.)
- I really don't know what it is... - In my opinion...
0分 0分
這麼一寫 真不知道
(If they can get at least 2, they can eat.)
- If we just get two right, we win. - Here we go.
在我看來 只要答對兩個就贏了
出題了
It's Lee Kwang Soo's turn.
李光洙
(Kwang Soo will try.)
I can't think of anything.
Don't even look at...
不做無用之工
Trees you can't climb.
不爲無益之事
(Correct!)
Trees you can't climb.
不爲無益之事
(What happened to Kwang Soo?)
Even dogs won't catch...
狗都不患
Winter colds.
冬季感冒
Summer colds.
五六月感冒
Winter colds!
冬季感冒
(Incorrect)
- Summer colds. - It's "summer".
-五六月感冒 -當然是夏天
- Summer colds. - Winter colds?
A lot of people catch colds in the winter.
冬天 冬天感冒很常見
- Winter colds - Okay.
冬天感冒呢
(Rationalizing himself)
- I was close, but I got it wrong. - Okay.
好 遺憾的答錯了
They say it's rustling...
簌簌響
(It's a question that's even hard for proverb expert Jae Seok.)
They say it's rustling...
簌簌響
Effortlessly?
輕輕地 什麼呀
What is that?
(They say it's rustling effortlessly?)
Effortlessly?
輕輕地 什麼呀
- That's not it. - What is it?
什麼來着 聲音什麼來着
(What's the first part?)
What was it? It was something related to sound.
The oak leaf says that the pine leaf is rustling.
枯葉嫌松葉簌簌響
- That's right. - That's it.
對 是這個是這個 對 知道知道
- I knew it. - This is important.
很難的
(It's a mix of hard and easy questions.)
- That's right. - This difficulty will be intense.
太難了
這個難易度太難了
This is hard.
好難
- This is hard. - This is the last question.
The sister-in-law is more irritating...
小姑更可恨
Than the mother-in-law who hits you.
打人的媽媽
- That's not it. - It's "who stops the fight is..."
不是不是
The sister-in-law who stops the fight is...
勸阻的小姑
勸阻的小姑更可恨
The mother-in-law who hits you.
(Kwang Soo got 1.)
In my opinion, we will get to eat if we get one question right.
我覺得應該能喫上
- You will get to eat. - You will get to eat.
感覺這個程度就能喫飯
(Jong Kook will try.)
- It's Kim Jong Kook's turn. - Okay, I'll try.
金鐘國
來了 我來吧
- It's really hard. - I think Jong Kook will be good.
太難了
(Jong Kook is unexpectedly good at this type of question.)
鍾國哥應該答得多
- I'm not sure. - It's hard.
不一定
- It's hard. - Let's get going.
-太難了 -太難了
來了
Your crotch will get ripped...
劈裂腿
Crane legs will also...
鶴腿
(Jong Kook can't do it either.)
It's "storks".
The crotch of crow-tits will get ripped if they follow storks.
東施效顰
- It's "storks". - Storks.
(He got it wrong, but he pretends to know it.)
Crow-tits were following storks.
(He said a crane, the long-legged bird, in a rush.)
- I get what you're talking about. - Crane legs.
我知道想說什麼
- Crane legs. - Crane legs.
懂吧
鶴腿
(It's really confusing.)
I knew what it was.
真的會混淆
- This is the second question. - This is hard.
第二個問題
You can't see through someone's mind...
一丈人心難知
Even if you know 1,000 fathoms of water,
千丈水流可知 一丈人心難知
you can't see through someone's mind.
- It's "10 fathoms of water". - 10 fathoms of water.
-十丈 -十丈 十丈
(It was close, but it's a wrong answer.)
Even if you know 1,000 fathoms of water,
千丈水流可知 一丈人心難知
you can't see through someone's mind.
- It's "10 fathoms of water". - It's "10 fathoms of water".
十丈
十丈 十丈
(It wasn't 1,000 but 10.)
是十丈
- It's confusing. - Gosh.
太混了
(Stop acting like you know.)
Please be quiet by his side.
在旁邊安靜一些
I said it after the bell was struck.
不是 是答錯後說出來的
(Speaking in Jeju dialect)
是答錯後說出來的
"I said it after..."
說出來了
- It's "10 fathoms of water". - It's "10 fathoms of water".
是十丈
(Jong Kook is struggling unexpectedly.)
This is the last question.
下一題
Jong Kook's proverbs are hard.
鍾國哥題好難
(Kwang Soo who got 1 is currently in the lead.)
We will get to eat if we get one question right.
我不是說過答一道題就能喫
You will get first place if you get two questions right.
答對兩個應該是第一
Rice cakes...
餅
Give one more rice cake to the child you hate? That's not it.
多給一個餅 不對啊
(Incorrect)
- Rice cakes you can't eat... - Rice cakes in drawings.
畫餅充飢
(He couldn't answer such an easy question.)
Rice cakes in drawings.
畫餅充飢
But this is...
但是這個
(Once they hear the answer, they know.)
- They just gave this to you. - Gosh.
這個是 這個是白給的題
- The last part is not enough. - It's hard. I can't think of it.
-這個聽 只聽後面的不知道 -太難了 太難了
It's easy after you hear the answer.
想不到
聽完覺得很簡單
(Jong Kook got 0.)
You don't know what it is.
不知道 不知道
I'm currently in first place.
現在第一
- It's Haha's turn. - Haha.
HAHA
(Haha will try.)
I'm getting confident though.
有自信了
To sow the wind...
惹重下兒
And reap the whirlwind!
輕下兒惹重下兒
(Correct!)
He's going to eat.
他應該能喫飯
There will be a hole to survive...
有出口
(Gibberish)
Needle.
針頭 不不
Needle!
針頭
(Because of So Min's distraction, he says "needle".)
Needle!
針頭 不不
針頭
- Did you say that? - Even mouse holes...
錯了
老鼠洞也有
Even if the sky collapses, there will be a hole to survive.
天塌下來也會有出口
(Embarrassed)
- It's not "mouse hole". - Gosh.
不是老鼠洞
- I'm angry. - How could you not know this?
好氣人
- This is a famous proverb. - How could you not know this?
這個怎麼沒想到呢
很有名的
This is the third question.
第三個問題
To deceive yourself...
盜鈴
- Cover your eyes! - This was easy.
掩耳
(Correct!)
Cover your eyes!
這個簡單
掩耳
- This was easy. - Cover your eyes...
這個簡單 這個簡單
(Haha's in the lead after getting 2 right.)
- Haha is in first place. - to deceive yourself.
-掩耳盜鈴 -HAHA第一
To be honest, his questions are too easy.
HAHA是第一
但是說實話他的太簡單了吧
(Angry)
- My questions were too hard. - That's right.
我的太難了
(The level of difficulty reflects their level of intelligence.)
- Ji Hyo's was tough too. - Okay, I got two.
-鍾國的很難 -鍾國哥的很難
-智孝的也很難 -兩個
The difficulty is too...
難易度太
(Because Haha did well, they complain.)
- There's too much of a difference. - How hard it will be for me?
差異太大了
(Feeling proud)
- Yes, it's like that. - Yes.
要給我多難的
有點那樣的
Haha, you're in first place.
哇 哥是第一
Whose turn is it now? Se Chan or So Min?
是世燦還是昭旻
(So Min will try.)
- It's So Min's turn. - That's right.
昭旻 之後是我
Junsobari.
全昭body
(She doesn't feel confident.)
- I don't think I'll get it right. - So Min.
-昭旻 -我感覺答得不多
They will go on top of the stove first...
先上鍋臺
A whimsical calf!
奇怪的小牛
(Whimsical So Min said the wrong answer.)
It's "well-behaved cat".
老實的小貓
(Embarrassed)
So Min, you...
昭旻 你
- I... - What did she say?
不是 突然想不起來
I suddenly didn't remember it.
- A whimsical calf? - She's really whimsical.
奇怪的小牛是什麼
(The relaxed man who answered 2 questions)
真的好奇怪
Wait a minute. Yes.
等一下
This is the second question.
第二個問題
A well-behaved cat?
老實的小貓
You will survive if you recover your senses...
只怕慌了神
- A crazy man... - What?
瘋子
老虎
(She throws wrong answers unhesitantly.)
瘋子
- It's "if you're in a tiger's den". - Wait a minute.
老虎 老虎洞 老虎洞
- It's "a tiger's den", isn't it? - A tiger's den.
等一下
是老虎洞吧 是吧 老虎洞裏
(How can you get this wrong?)
- This was too easy. - This was too easy.
-簡單 -這個太簡單了
(They all raise their voices when it's someone else's question.)
- How could you not know this? - Even if you're in a tiger's den...
兩個都
-這個不能不知道 -去老虎洞也是
(It's the next question.)
This is the third question.
來 第三道題
You can't give it to dogs...
難移
- Someone else's habits! - What is this?
他性
(Incorrect)
- It's "your habits". - It's "your habits".
-本性 -本性
- Your habits. - This was too easy.
這個太簡單了
- To someone else? - To dogs.
給別人
本性 本性
- In my opinion, the meanings... - It's easy when you hear it.
-我看來 -聽後就簡單
(Giving a lame excuse in front of her husband)
- of what I said are similar. - That's right.
意思都差不多 我說的
- Only the details were wrong. - "A well-behaved cat"...
對 對
細節不一樣
(Still, "An eccentric cow" was...)
老實的小貓和
and "An eccentric cow" are entirely different.
-奇怪的小牛 -奇怪的小牛
I said the first thing that came to my mind.
太不一樣了
突然想起來的是
(So Min got 0.)
- Let's go. - You become dazed.
來 梁世燦
(Se Chan will try next.)
- Se Chan. - Here I go.
梁世body
- Let's go. - Try to get one right.
我來了
-多對一點 世燦 -準備 來了
Out of the blue.
敲棒槌
(He just needs to get one question right in order to eat!)
Out of the blue.
敲棒槌
- A squid. - A bolt!
短蛸
大半夜
(It's the easiest question so far.)
- A bolt. - Hey, it was a really easy one.
-大半夜 -太簡單了
I will have no expectations. I have zero expectations.
不期待了 不期待 我不期待了
I can't tease him because it's unbelievable.
這個有點不敢捉弄 因爲是真的
You know how it is.
到自己答題的時候會嗎
(The pencil squid's lame excuse)
I couldn't say what I know due to nerves.
我知道也這樣
A goby also jumps.
彈塗魚也跟着跳
When a pencil squid jumps, a goby also jumps.
短蛸跳 彈塗魚也跟着跳 不是這個嗎
(He sounds like a pencil squid that is upset.)
When a pencil squid jumps, a goby also jumps.
短蛸跳 彈塗魚也跟着跳 不是這個嗎
- When a gray mullet jumps... - Is it a gray mullet?
鯔魚一跳
- Yes, it's a gray mullet. - It isn't a pencil squid.
是鯔魚嗎
(When a gray mullet jumps, a goby also jumps.)
I thought it was a pencil squid.
-不是短蛸 -不是短蛸
以爲是短蛸跳 彈塗魚也跟着跳
(One who copies someone better than him without realizing his situation)
This is the last question.
最後一題
He didn't get a single question right.
一道也沒答對
With acorns.
橡子
(He must get this question right in order to eat!)
With acorns.
橡子
Comparing the heights!
量身高
(You must get the first half.)
- That's wrong. - It's "With acorns".
前面的
Dog food.
後面的是量身高
狗食裏的 狗食裏的
(Se Chan didn't get anything.)
- It's so embarrassing. - The production crew is laughing.
最有自信的
Comparing the heights!
怎麼說了橡子量身高
(The wife is embarrassed of her husband.)
- The newlyweds are out. - That was hilarious.
這邊的夫婦
(Seok Jin will try next.)
- Excuse me. - Seok Jin.
真的好搞笑
那個
I will show you the perfect score.
池石鎮
給你們展示滿分
(He seems like an expert from his outfit.)
- Seok Jin. - Okay.
池石鎮
(He's an old man.)
Seok Jin knows a lot of proverbs.
是
石鎮哥懂很多俗語
- Let's begin. - Okay.
-開始啦 -OK
Looks at the roof.
徒望屋脊
Dog... Dr. Dog.
狗 狗博士
- Dr. Dog? - Dr. Dog?
-狗博士 狗博士 -追雞之犬
(He was condescending.)
He said he can get all the proverbs right.
這個別人的都答對 自己
Hold on. Gosh.
等一下 這個突然開始 想不起來
(Master Jee is embarrassed.)
I knew it had something to do with "Dog".
I couldn't think of it.
想不起來
- I didn't know... - A dog that was chasing a chicken.
-追雞之犬 -是狗 但是不知道是什麼狗
- what kind of dog it was. - Let's go.
You glare at the Han River.
開始啦
到漢江才瞪眼
After scowling.
盯住
- Isn't it "After getting slapped"? - After getting slapped at Jongno.
-鍾路上被扇耳光 -不是扇耳光嗎
Is that it?
是那樣嗎
Where did "After scowling" come from?
盯住是什麼
(Seok Sam's common knowledge is low despite his experience.)
I couldn't think of it.
想不起來
(He kept showing off.)
You kept going, "How could you not know that?"
裝作很懂 還耀武揚威
- "After scowling"? - After scowling.
-盯住 -盯住
(Embarrassed)
I suddenly couldn't remember it.
想不起來 突然
- Let's resume. - Okay.
-開始啦 -來吧
- A chicken. - A dog that was chasing a chicken!
雞
追雞之犬
A dog that was chasing a chicken!
- My goodness. - What is it?
What is the answer?
-雞什麼 -雞什麼
(He was just laughing at "comparing the heights with acorns".)
- Not a pheasant, but a chicken. - Not a pheasant, but a chicken.
-以雞代雉 -以雞代雉
- What is up with you? - You should try it!
這哥怎麼回事
(Blaming)
You shouldn't have been so snobby.
-你試試 -不要裝懂了
- You should try it. - After getting the same proverb,
你試試
(He's dressed as a proverb master,)
(but he's actually a dog that was chasing a chicken.)
you went, "A dog that was chasing a chicken!"
追雞之犬都出來了還說追雞之犬
This is the last question. To Gangnam.
最後的問題
去江南
(Will he be able to get the first part right?)
- You follow your friend. - That was easy.
-跟着朋友 -這個
(Correct)
Hold on!
好簡單
- You follow your friend. - This is easy.
-跟着朋友 -這個
Hold on! Why did he get such an easy one?
好簡單
但是 等一下 這種
(That was so easy.)
- Okay. - It was too easy.
-OK -好簡單
(I would've got that too.)
- It was too easy. - Seriously.
-這個真的 這個 -真的簡單
- I mean... - It was too easy.
-不是 -OK
(Seok Jin got 1 question right.)
好簡單
I will go next.
那就輪到我
(Lastly, Jae Seok will try.)
- Jae Seok. - All right.
來 劉在錫
(You yelled at me.)
- Let's see how well you can do. - You know,
嗯 看看你能答對多少
I need to get 1 or 2 questions right.
-這個要答對一兩個才能喫飯 -因爲是三秒
(If he answers at least one right,)
You only get three seconds.
(he gets to eat and exempted from the tour cost.)
You just need to get one question right.
應該起碼答對一個的
Let's begin.
開始啦
And meat is for chewing.
肉不嚼不香
(He often flaunted his knowledge to other members.)
(Will the human cultural asset get it right?)
(What will be Jae Seok's answer?)
- What? - Song Dae Kwan.
-什麼 -宋大琯老師 宋大琯
(Time's up.)
- Insadol. - What?
Insadol（牙痛藥）
- Song Dae Kwan. - Insadol.
-什麼 -宋大琯老師 宋大琯
You need strong teeth.
Insadol
牙要好
(Chew, bite, taste, and enjoy.)
- Song Dae Kwan. - Insadol.
-宋大琯老師 -Insadol
Which proverb ends with "And meat is for chewing"?
肉不嚼不香是什麼
- What is that? - What is that?
-什麼 -這是什麼
Words are for talking and meat is for chewing.
-話不說不明 肉不嚼不香  -啊
- That sounds familiar. - It's so difficult.
(Groaning)
這個好難 爲什麼這麼難
Why is it so difficult? The difficulty level is too high.
(The human cultural asset couldn't say anything from the start.)
對啊
這個太難了
Gets no wind.
沒有風停的日子
This one is easy.
-這個 -這個簡單
- It's easy. - What was it? A household?
什麼來着
家裏
A household?
喂 家裏嗎 裝得這麼懂來着
(A household with no wind)
You were being so cocky earlier.
- What is it? - A tree with many branches.
是什麼
- A tree with many branches. - A tree with many branches.
枝繁葉茂的樹
-啊 枝繁葉茂的樹 -枝繁葉茂的樹
Gosh, I knew this proverb. I have to get one right.
不是不知道的
這個應該答對的 要瘋了
You only remember it after you hear the answer.
-聽完之後就知道了 -要瘋了
- Okay. - That was funny.
-OK -OK
He might not be able to eat.
他答不對就吃不了了
Keep you awake all night long.
不知道天亮
- This one is easy. - Late-learned thieving skills...
-這個好簡單 -晚學的小偷不知道天亮
keep you awake all night long.
(Correct)
I thought it was "Thieving for the first time".
我還以爲是第一個小偷
Who came in last?
最後一名是誰
There must be many people.
最後一名有幾個吧
(The 4 who didn't get anything)
- We came in last. - 4 people got 0 questions right.
我們好像是最後一名
- 4 people? - There is space for 1 more person.
0分四名 0分
四名嗎
(One of them can eat.)
-但是有一個可以喫 -OK
Why don't the four of you play rock-paper-scissors?
四名中猜拳選一名喫嗎
(Whoever answers the question will get to eat.)
Why don't you give us the same question?
要不然就出同一問題 首先答對的人
- The one who answers should eat. - Shall we do that?
-OK -要那樣嗎
Let's go.
嗯
開始啦
And he asks to give you his bag.
交出包袱
Talk to a porter and he asks to give you his bag.
叫腳伕交出包袱
(Se Chan is out.)
(Jae Seok has a problem remembering someone else's question.)
- Gosh, it's so easy. - Do you know it?
-這個 太 -你知道這個嗎
You spare a man and he asks to give you his bag.
太簡單了
這個爲什麼不知道
救了人還叫我交出包袱
(Incorrect)
Save a man from drowning and he asks to give you his bag.
啊 救了落水的人還叫我交出包袱
(Jong Kook gets it right.)
- There you go. - That's right.
-對啦 -對
Save a man from drowning and he asks to give you his bag.
-救了落水的人還叫我交出包袱 -那段
(They place last.)
- Okay. - Is that the first part?
-對啦  -那前面的 那前面的
- The first part. - Save a man from drowning.
(Retrieving his reputation)
- That's right. - Jong Kook succeeded.
-金鐘國成功 -OK
Why isn't it about a porter?
都給腳伕吧 真是的
Save a man from drowning and he asks to give you his bag.
-腳伕 -救了落水的人還叫我交出包袱
(Third mission result)
It's about a drowning man.
前面的水是重點
Thus,
所以宋智孝 全昭旻 梁世燦除外的人用餐
(The familiar three placed last.)
five members except for Ji Hyo, So Min, and Se Chan will eat.
Okay.
好
(They acquire a stamp.)
- The cutoff line... - What is this?
大衣
-哇 這是什麼 -我的天
(They enjoy a course meal with a sunset.)
Oh, my goodness!
- It's the braised hairtail. - What is this?
這是燉菜啊 燉菜 辣燉帶魚 -這是什麼
(It's full of fresh ingredients of Jeju Island.)
- What is this? - What is this?
-這是什麼 -這是什麼
This is a meal you must eat.
這個一定要喫
It's tasty.
好好喫
(Running Tour provides a proper meal.)
Order me some food too.
- It's so tasty. - Thank you.
好好喫
Thank you for the meal.
-謝謝 -我開喫啦
(The bottom 3 can only have seafood pastes.)
- We got this dish. - Let's mix it with rice.
-姐姐 -拌飯
Do you want some hairtail?
那邊想喫帶魚嗎
(Do you want some hairtail?)
(Interested)
- Yes! - Do you want some hairtail?
-想 -想
(We want hairtail.)
Please give us some.
-那邊想喫帶魚嗎 -分點給我們
Please give us a piece.
就一小塊
(Seok Jin will ask a question...)
Then you should get a question right.
那要答對問題嗎
(and whoever answers it will get hairtail.)
What question?
什麼
I will give you three seconds. Can I decide on a member?
給你三秒
- Devotion will touch the sky. - I mean...
可以指定嗎
-至誠 感天 -可不可以指定
- Can I decide on a member? - Devotion...
可以指定嗎
(The proverb quiz left Se Chan traumatized.)
- will touch the sky. - I mean...
-至誠 感天 -可不可以指定
He asked if he can decide on the member.
問可不可以指定 指定
- I will decide on Ji Hyo. - Okay.
-指定宋智孝 -好
Travels 400km.
行千里
A foot without words...
-一 -足 足無話
足 足無話 話無足
- A word without feet... - A foot without words!
-足無話 -對不起
(I shouldn't have done that.)
- I am sorry. - A word without feet.
(She can't laugh because Ji Hyo tried her best.)
I am sorry.
-話無足 -對不起
I can't believe she said, "A foot without words".
-話無足 -足無話 足無話
- A word without feet... - A foot without words!
-足無話 足無話 -急了 急了
(Still confused)
- A foot without words! - She was in a hurry.
The wrong proverb suits Ji Hyo.
但是俗語和智孝很合適
The losers will play a game to decide who will pay.
在用餐的時候
(It's time to pick who will pay among the losers.)
要進行在敗北者中選出結算人的遊戲
- Yes. - That's right.
-是啊 -嗯嗯
(Team Asst. Manager Ha and the Recruit is safe.)
- Thank goodness both of us won. - I know.
幸好我們倆都不用
- I will give you the game. - Okay.
-告訴你們選定結算人遊戲 -嗯
(After playing the game to pick the person to pay,)
Se Chan will pay.
梁世燦當選結算人
(Se Chan will pay.)
Okay!
OK
- You lost. - That was pretty far.
你是最後一名
(The course meal costs...)
- The total of the meal is... - How much is it?
到得挺遠的啊
這個金額是
多少錢
- 374 dollars. - What?
-374000韓元 -這麼少
(Sad)
It isn't as expensive as I thought.
-比想象中要少 -沒多少
The first place was the most expensive.
第一次的最貴
(This is bad.)
You ate a lot. The total is 370 dollars.
吃了很多了 37萬韓元的話
We will get coffee to go...
打包一杯咖啡 完成最終任務就結束
(They will move to the last mission place.)
- and move on to the last mission. - Okay.
OK
- We should turn the tables. - Let's do that.
-最後我們要決勝負 -決勝負吧
(They completed the course.)
(Now that they're full, it's time to get some coffee.)
What comes now isn't a mission.
現在不是任務
You just need to go to the cafe and order coffee to go.
-就是去咖啡店點單打包咖啡 -OK
- Really? - Who wants to go?
-真的嗎 -哪位做代表
(We will go.)
We will go.
-我們 -那個
No, no. My pupil is here.
-我們有弟子 -有弟子啊
- Your pupil. - Seok Sam can go.
(Student and slave at the same time)
- Your pupil. - Listen.
石三去就行
I have a few pupils too.
不是 我下面也有點人
- Like who? - What?
誰啊
Didn't you say you were born in 2002?
-你 -剛剛不是說是02年出生嗎 石三
- He was born in 2004. - 2004.
什麼
-04 04 -啊 04
(It's hard to believe, but he's in Grade 10.)
In which year were you born?
不是 那你是什麼時候出生的
2001.
我是01
- He is older. - You are older.
-那你是哥啊 -嗯
(How rude.)
Why are you speaking so casually to an older boy?
怎麼跟哥說非敬語
(Seok Sam hasn't learned manners yet.)
- Seok Sam. - Why do I need to...
-石三啊 -我
Why did I become someone who was born in 2004?
糊里糊塗地說是04年出生
(Angry)
Seok Sam, I can't believe you!
石三你怎麼 你真的是
(You'll be scolded.)
Do you want me to whip your legs?
-那個 -將你腿
What about my legs?
腿嗎 不是
(Meanwhile)
- He is polite to Jae Seok. - Listen.
-還認真地說了敬語 -那個
(Changing the target)
You look young. Why don't you go?
那邊看着很年輕 去吧
(Are you interested in me?)
Are you interested in me?
感興趣嗎
(Laughing)
He is happy.
-石三 -喜歡了 喜歡了
(She attacks Seok Sam's heart, who never had a girlfriend before.)
- He is happy. - He is single.
-單身 剛剛說是單身來着-被發現心思了
He said earlier that he is single.
Since I am going through puberty, I am interested.
處在青春期 也不是不感興趣
-石三不要踩界 -說是處在青春期
(She's mine.)
- Seok Sam, stay in your lane. - He is going through puberty!
-石三不要踩界 -說是處在青春期
(Shy Seok Sam is going through puberty.)
- He is going through puberty! - This is insane.
真是要瘋了
The newlyweds and Seok Sam should go.
-新婚夫妻和石三去買 -好 挺好
(Anyway, the newlywed couple and Seok Sam will get a takeout.)
That's a good idea.
We will go together.
好的 哥 一起去吧
Seok Sam, let's go together.
好的 我們帶石三一起去吧
Okay, Seok Sam.
好的 石三啊
(Why did I become a boy who was born in 2004?)
Why did I become a boy who was born in 2004?
爲什麼給我的人設是04年生
(Seok Sam.)
- Wait for us. - Seok Sam, wait for us.
-得一起走呀 -石三啊 一起走吧
(Moving fast)
Okay.
好的 好的 姐姐
(Seok Sam listens to So Min well.)
- How pretty! - Seom and Some.
-約會啊 -島與島
(A view where you can see the ocean at a glance...)
- Hello. - Hello.
-你好 -你好
- How pretty! It's pretty here. - Hello.
-好漂亮 -歡迎
I really like this.
-你好 -漂亮漂亮
我很喜歡這個的 這個
(with mouthwatering desserts)
Let's buy some bread too.
-我們也買點麪包吧 -買吧
- Let's do that. - Shall we get the corn sticks?
-買麪包吧 這個 -買玉米茶嗎
(They place an order first excitedly.)
Two cups of iced chamomile tea.
兩杯涼爽的焦糖瑪奇朵
The bread is incredible.
這麪包絕了
(They check out the cafe after placing an order.)
This is where you take photos.
哥 這裏是拍照的地方啊
Where?
-這裏 -這裏 哇
- My goodness. - Hey.
-新婚夫妻 -好漂亮
- How pretty! - Shall I take a photo of you guys?
(You can enjoy the night in Jeju here.)
It would look really beautiful during the day.
要給你們拍照嗎
夜景真的好美
This is where you take photos.
哥 這裏是拍照的地方
I will take a photo of you guys.
嗯 我給你們拍照吧
(Seok Sam takes photos of them.)
- Okay. - My goodness.
這裏 這裏絕了
This is an amazing spot.
1, 2, 3.
1 2 3
(We are newlyweds for the day. Seok Sam, take nice photos.)
- Give me the phone now. - You should get your photos taken.
大哥 大哥 把手機給我吧
(It's time to take Seok Sam's photos.)
也幫哥哥拍一張
Should I keep my mask on?
戴着口罩嗎
- Smile. - 1, 2, 3.
請微笑
1 2 3
(He poses like he went to college in the 80s and 90s,)
1, 2, 3. Let's do this.
-1 2 我們來這邊拍吧 -嗯
(Are you taking good photos of me?)
Smile.
稍等 注意一下表情 哥
- Smile. - 1, 2, 3.
請微笑
1 2 3
(He is taking selfies.)
1, 2, 3. Let's move a bit here.
-1 2 來這邊 真的 這裏這樣 -嗯
(The swindler couple is busy taking selfies.)
- Let's take it like this. - It's prettier.
-這邊好 -這裏更好看
1, 2, 3.
這裏好 1 2 3
(Seok Sam is excited.)
- Let's take it like this. - It's prettier.
來這邊 真的 這裏這樣 -嗯
-這邊好 -這裏更好看
(Making a V-sign)
1, 2, 3.
這裏好 1 2 3
It came out really well.
-OK -拍出來的成品非常好
(He is excited to see the photos.)
(Se Chan runs away after fooling him.)
- This is nice. - When you come to Jeju Island,
-果然 -好美
來濟州島的話 哥
you should take a lot of photos.
就得拍很多照片的
(He sees the newlywed couple.)
Hold on. Hey.
喂 怎麼都是...
Did you guys take selfies?
-自拍了嗎 -是的
(It's okay.)
You took selfies. Okay.
啊 自拍了啊 好
(Seok Sam is a bit foolish,)
It's okay. It's okay to take selfies like that.
沒關係 有可能這麼拍的
(but he's kind.)
That's what you do when you are newlyweds.
因爲新婚的時候
This place is the best.
都是自拍的
這裏是藝術啊 這裏
The two of you should sit here.
你倆坐這裏來 這裏
(Seok Sam's going to take photos of them again.)
Here?
這裏嗎
What a shot!
你看這 看這
Make a heart over your heads.
比心比心 頭頂比心
- That's so old. - Go ahead and make a heart.
頭頂比心都是什麼時候的事了
- That's so old. - Come on.
來一次頭頂比心嘛
頭頂比心都是什麼時候的事了
One... Go ahead and do it.
來一下嘛 1
(They soon make a heart after complaining.)
1, 2, 3.
來一下來一下 1 2 3
- I should work with cameras. - Why?
看來攝像頭很棒啊
(Look at this.)
Are you good at taking photos?
怎麼了
照片拍出來還不錯嗎 哥哥
(Another best photo with the beautiful night view of Jeju)
This is a work of art.
真的是藝術
- You take good photos. - That's a nice photo.
-拍得很好啊 -拍得很好啊
- You take good photos of your wife. - Yes, I do.
-哥哥也很會幫嫂子拍照吧 -嗯
(This time)
- I will take your photos for real. - No.
大哥也拍一張吧
-真的給你拍一次照 -不不
- I am serious. - Seok Jin.
-哥哥拍一張吧 真的 -真的 哥 哥
(You can't fool me.)
- I don't need photos. - I am serious.
-我不拍照 -不騙你
真的 哥 真的來一張 真的幫你拍
I will take them for real.
(He heads to the photo zone forcibly.)
- You need photos from here. - I don't want to do that.
-得拍一張的 -我不喜歡拍照的
I don't like what I am wearing.
衣服也是黑不溜秋的
(Despite the complaints, he poses in an old-fashioned way.)
- It's a good shot. - One...
-很上鏡啊 -1
(He zoomed in on Seok Jin's face.)
(This photographer eliminated the background.)
I will focus on your face.
-我拍照以人物爲主 -1
One...
I feel bad for him.
(You can't tell if he is in Jeju Island or Yeouido.)
Okay. You don't need to take many photos.
OK
可以了 不用拍多少
He is handsome.
石鎮哥哥長得好帥啊
He is handsome. Seok Jin is handsome, isn't he?
石鎮哥哥長得好帥啊 對吧
I focus on the face when I take photos.
我拍照的時候以人物爲主
(He checks the photo excitedly.)
I see.
啊 這樣啊
- I don't focus on the background. - It's nice.
-我不在意背景 以人物爲主 -真好
(Chuckling)
(Zoomed in)
- What do you think? - You...
這也太...
You zoomed in too much.
-鏡頭拉得也太近了吧 -是的
I focused on the face.
以人物爲主
(The background only assists.)
- I focused on the face. - You zoomed in too much.
我拍照以人物爲主
(While the three enjoy their time,)
Be careful.
-鏡頭拉得也太近了 -沒錯
Let's get going now. Is our order ready?
-現在走吧 -好的 哥
-都好了嗎 -嗯
(others are waiting inside the bus.)
- Five years? - Yes.
-55嗎 -嗯
(Wriggling)
That must be nice.
挺好
(He is distracted.)
You aren't a human cultural asset, are you?
老師不是非物質文化遺產吧
(He is too unfocused to be a human cultural asset.)
What do you do for a living?
你真正的職業什麼啊
(Not a human cultural asset)
Aren't you a human problem?
你真正的職業什麼啊
是人類問題吧
(The human cultural asset seems to have a lot of issues.)
- I am a human cultural asset. - A human problem.
-非物質文化遺產 -是人類問題
非物質文化遺產
My drawing of an orchid...
我畫一幅畫的話 價值2到3000萬韓元
costs 20,000 to 30,000 dollars.
(Then)
You are an artist.
-這個 -畫 畫家
- Do you have a nickname? - What?
-有暱稱嗎 暱稱 -誰
(That's a pen name.)
- A pen name? - Something like a pen name.
-那是號 號 -號
(It's suspicious how he joined Running Trading Company.)
How could you call it a nickname?
暱稱
A nickname?
竟然說成暱稱
You make it sound like a nickname from school days.
你是在問外號嗎 上學時的外號
Something like a silly goose.
河代理
外號 調皮鬼調皮鬼這種的
(The recruit is embarrassed of his boss.)
A nickname! A nickname!
暱稱 暱稱
What's your pen name?
號是什麼啊 號是什麼啊
(He doesn't want to talk to Haha.)
Do I really need to reveal it to someone like him?
我得向這種朋友解釋嗎
是什麼啊
I am not sure if you would know, but...
我吧 不知道各位知不知道
Do you know who Johns Hopkins is?
知道約翰·霍普金斯嗎
(American businessman who founded Johns Hopkins University)
- That came out of nowhere. - Johns Hopkins.
這麼突然嗎
- He is a famous painter. - That's right, I respect him a lot.
嗯 約翰·霍普金斯
是一位著名的畫家
是的 是我十分尊敬的一位
(Reading the room)
That's right, I respect him a lot.
是一位著名的畫家
是的 是我十分尊敬的一位
(What are you talking about?)
Did you just say Johns Hopkins is a famous painter?
-約翰·霍普金斯 -約翰·霍普金斯
是著名畫家嗎
(No ordinary person understands the Olympiad level of knowledge.)
- This is insane. - This is insane.
真是要瘋了
I can't have a conversation with them.
我怎麼會和這些人聊這個話題
(I've heard about it before.)
- What? - Johns Hopkins.
怎麼了 爲什麼這麼說
- Johns Hopkins. - He is a famous painter, right?
-約翰·霍普金斯 -約翰·霍普金斯
- Is he a stock investor? - What?
是著名畫家吧
-那個 炒股的人嗎 -啥
(Not John Lee)
He asked if he is a stock investor.
炒股的人
Seriously.
(Favorite painter)
Johns Hopkins.
約翰·霍普金斯
(Then)
Do you have a favorite work of his?
那位所畫的畫中有喜歡的畫嗎
- Yes. - What is it?
-是的 -有嗎
(Gibberish)
"Deviation".
叛逆 叛逆
(Gibberish)
My favorite is "Jonathan's River".
我喜歡喬納森的江
(Saying everything they know)
"Jonathan's River".
-喬納森的江 -嗯
- "Jonathan's River". - It draws you in.
-喬納森的江 -總感覺會沉迷
(Brazen)
It's so frustrating to talk to them.
真鬱悶 我和這些人聊這個
Why aren't you saying anything?
不過你爲什麼不說話啊
Are you laughing because you understand it?
你知道我們在說什麼才笑的嗎
Of course.
知道知道
(Respect it if you don't know.)
- I respect him. - You respect him.
我很尊敬 很尊敬
-很尊敬嗎 -嗯
All right. Make light work.
-好 -他是做什麼的人呢
兩個人擡着輕
(A sudden quiz)
Let's.
好好
(That's ingenious.)
(It's incorrect, but it's not exactly wrong.)
That works too.
對 說得也沒錯
(The Olympiad winner also has a sense of humor.)
- She is witty. - She is witty.
很有才氣
She is witty.
-有才氣 -有才氣
- That cafe is a work of art. - Why?
哇 那裏是藝術啊
(Meanwhile, the 3 ordered the takeout.)
It's so nice.
爲什麼
非常棒 非常棒
It's so nice.
Is it by the sea?
大海就在眼前嗎 大海
It's more than that. It's so big.
是的 姐姐 不只是這樣
地方非常的大
Here you go.
The packaging is pretty.
包裝也很漂亮
Thank you.
-我開動了 -我開動了
- Okay. - Who is paying for this?
-OK -這是誰買回來的
Seok Sam, thank you for the coffee.
石三啊 謝謝你
(Half formal, half informal)
- Okay. - Is Seok Sam paying for this?
-嗯 嗯 好好 -這是石三哥哥買回來的嗎
It will be included in the total.
就這樣成爲了最後決定性的環節了
(They go to the location of the last mission!)
The total wasn't that big.
不過沒剩下多少了
Do you see the powder here?
有甜味
(So far, the customers are satisfied with Running Tour's package trip.)
Are you satisfied with the trip?
各位 滿意這裏嗎
- Yes. - It's perfect.
很完美
I will now explain which course remains.
要說剩下的旅行行程的話
(It's finally the last course.)
Give us a chance to turn the tables.
給我們能反轉的機會吧
(They can turn the tables in the final course.)
- You can turn the tables. - Really?
能反轉的機會
-完全可以逆轉的 -是嗎
All right. The best part of flying is...
-飛機旅行的亮點是機內免稅店吧 -是的
(If there's an inflight duty-free shop in the plane,)
- the in-flight duty-free shop. - Yes.
(there's an inside-the-car duty-free shop in the bus.)
On the bus,
我們在車內就可以直接買紀念品
- you can purchase a souvenir. - Really?
(Each team can buy 1 souvenir.)
- Each team can choose 1 souvenir. - 1?
真的嗎
每個隊可以選擇一種紀念品
(They were supposed to stop somewhere for the souvenirs.)
There is something I need to tell you in advance.
-一種 -一種
在這之前我要說的是
Since we don't have time to visit a souvenir shop,
本來我們得去一個地方買的
(Due to tight schedule,)
So Min will sacrifice her free time and go with us tomorrow.
但是時間不夠了
全昭旻決定和老師明天一起去買
(So Min will buy their souvenirs for them.)
- Good job. - If you agree, we will give her...
做得好
所以各位同意的話
(It's a gift from staff for So Min who cares about the show.)
- a penalty exemption card. - I will go tomorrow.
決定給她一張懲罰免除券
(If everyone agrees, So Min will get a penalty exemption card.)
- So Min? - Yes.
我去買
-昭旻嗎 -嗯
- She is staying another day. - We will give it to her.
-多待一天 -給昭旻
- Okay. - A penalty exemption card.
-嗯 -嗯
(Since she's spending more time for them, they all agree.)
- Really? - You will have a shoot tomorrow.
-給一張免除券 -真的嗎 真的嗎
-當然 你明天還得拍攝呢 -明天還得拍攝
(A penalty exemption card is given to So Min for future.)
- Thank you. - If you don't want it...
謝謝
- I want it. Give it to me. - It's yours.
-拒絕這個提議的話 -不 我喜歡的
Choose a souvenir So Min will buy it tomorrow.
-收下吧 收下吧 -給我吧
所以每隊挑一個
(They'll choose the souvenirs that So Min will buy the next day.)
-讓全昭旻去買的紀念品 -好的
- Okay. - Let's see.
讓我看看
(Jeju Island souvenir menu)
Let's see.
讓我看看
- The hairtail set. - It's expensive.
-帶魚套裝 -挺貴啊
(Seafood products, agricultural products)
It's the real deal.
是真的啊
(Industrial products)
I want to buy wine.
我要買紅酒
- I like tilefish. - Tilefish is the best.
-鯛魚挺好的 -濟州島肯定是鯛魚
(Alcohol)
- It has a long face. - Then...
哪種有紀念意義
you should take a hairtail set to your parents.
-我們買帶魚 然後石三給父母送去 -謝謝
(A lesson from the human cultural asset...)
Thank you.
- It's for you, Seok Sam. - The hairtail.
石三
(for Seok Sam who isn't a good son)
Yes, the hairtail.
-這邊選帶魚 -嗯 帶魚
(The newlywed couple chooses Jeju tangerine wine.)
We want tangerine wine.
我們買濟州柑橘紅酒
- Tangerine wine. - Let's drink wine.
-濟州柑橘紅酒 -對
We also want tangerine wine.
我們也選濟州柑橘紅酒
- Let's eat cheonhyehyang. - Aren't you a student?
你們是學生可以喝酒嗎
- Seriously. - That's wrong.
-是啊 這個 -因爲
(The human cultural asset is mad at the delinquent.)
- Hey, hey. - Get the hairtail set.
這不行
去帶魚吧帶魚
Get the hairtail set.
帶魚帶魚
- Seaweed chips. - Eat hairtail.
-就去帶魚吧 -紫菜鍋巴
He looks like seaweed chips, so that should be his souvenir.
他長得像紫菜鍋巴就給他紫菜鍋巴吧
(Angry)
- Hairtail. - How could you say that?
帶魚
你說什麼啊
- You look like seaweed chips. - It's your hair.
你長得像紫菜鍋巴
(Kwang Soo ends up choosing a hairtail.)
- I will get the hairtail set. - Hairtail.
我們選濟州帶魚套餐
(Team Running Trading Company made a choice too.)
The total cost of the coffee...
帶魚 好
所以剛剛咖啡費用
(The coffee and souvenirs...)
and the expensive souvenirs you have chosen is...
可能比大家想象中要貴
(cost 773 dollars.)
- 773 dollars. - What?
77萬3千韓元
That's the worst.
這個完全是完蛋了
(The team that pays 773 dollars...)
I forgot about the coffee.
有咖啡啊
(is guaranteed to lose.)
The last mission will change the rankings.
那麼局面完全會翻盤啊
(The final mission to determine the loser)
- I will explain the last mission. - Okay.
-好 說明最後的任務 -好
- Soon, we will arrive at a cafe. - Okay.
-稍後將會到達一家咖啡店 -好的
(Soon, they will arrive at a cafe.)
(Each team will enter the cafe every 1 minute.)
Two team members will decide on the order...
每隊兩名隊員按照順序
and enter the cafe every one minute.
相隔1分鐘進入咖啡店
(If they stay unrecognized, they win.)
It's your mission to stay without getting recognized.
堅持不被發現就勝利
- By whom? - Only the cafe owner knows.
被誰發現
現在只有老闆知道
(Aside from the cafe owner,)
The part-timers and customers don't know about the shoot.
兼職生和客人完全不知道
(the part-timers and customers don't know about the shoot.)
- I have an advantage. - How about the cameras?
鏡頭怎麼辦
(The staff members are ready to film!)
The staff members are already hiding in the cafe.
我們全都在角落藏着
(Each team will enter the cafe every 1 minute.)
Two members will enter the cafe at a time.
定好順序
先兩個人進去
The 2nd team will enter after 1 minute.
然後1分鐘後再兩個人進去
(The team that gets the name called first loses and pays for the cost.)
If your name gets called, you are out.
接着首先被喊出名字的隊伍淘汰
("You are so-and-so, right?")
- That team will get the penalty. - What if...
然後接受懲罰
What if someone says, "You look familiar?"
比如說 好像在哪裏見過你 還是說
(Their exact names have to be called to lose.)
- No, your name has to be called. - Your name.
不 要喊出名字纔行
Wait until everyone enters the cafe.
名字
要等到別人都進去的時候
(If it doesn't end after all four teams enter,)
If all eight members enter without any names being called,
要是意外地大家都進去了
但是誰也沒被認出來
(they will take turns to order drinks.)
then you need to take turns to order the drinks too.
那麼就要按照順序下單飲料
- Can I take off my glasses? - Of course.
可以脫眼鏡吧
- People don't recognize me. - We are allowed...
可以
大家都不太認得我
(They're allowed to wear a hat and a mask.)
- to cover our faces, right? - Can we wear...
戴帽子遮臉也可以吧
- a hat? - You can wear a mask and a hat.
可以戴帽子嗎
口罩和帽子都可以
(Glancing)
Can we wear sunglasses?
墨鏡可以嗎
But I am wearing modern hanbok.
但是衣服是改良的韓服
(Stealing attention)
But I am wearing modern hanbok. It will catch people's eyes.
但是衣服是改良的韓服
應該會被發現吧
- You should wear a jacket. - This is bad.
穿夾克 夾克
出大事了
Let's play Race of Wits for the order.
穿夾克纔行
那麼玩眼色遊戲決定吧
(They'll play Race of Wits for the order.)
- The losers go first. - Yes.
眼色遊戲
那麼輸了的隊伍先去
(It's disadvantageous to enter early.)
嗯
- It's Race of Wits. - Race of Wits.
玩眼色遊戲啦
(Who will enter first?)
Don't stand up. Call out the number.
眼色遊戲眼色遊戲
不用站起來 就喊號碼
(Race of Wits begins.)
- Get ready. - Set.
準備
開
- Set. - I will go first.
-我一定先喊 -開
- I will go fourth. - Go.
我是1啊1
始
One.
- 2. - 3.
- 4. - 5.
- 6. - 2.
- 3. - 4.
- 5. - 6.
-4 -5
- 7. - 7.
-7 -7
- Okay. - 5.
(Seok Sam and Kwang Soo lose.)
- 6. - 7.
-7 -7
Rock-paper-scissors.
剪刀石頭布 剪刀石頭布
(Seok Sam loses every game.)
He is so cute.
哎喲真可愛
(Teasing)
- Kwang Soo is cute. - Kwang Soo is cute.
光洙真可愛
(Seok Sam and Kwang Soo somehow became rivals.)
- Kwang Soo is cute. - He is cute.
光洙真可愛
光洙好可愛
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
好可愛
剪刀石頭布
(Team Olympiad will go first.)
- Okay. - What happens if Kwang Soo goes...
OK
(If they get caught as soon as they enter, it's over.)
and gets caught?
光洙一進去被發現的話怎麼辦
- Then it's game over. - Is it game over?
那就結束了
(Team Olympiad is expected to end the mission fast.)
That won't do. Don't send in Kwang Soo first.
不可以光洙不可以進去了
No, no. You just need to hang in for a minute.
不是不是
相隔1分鐘
(The order of entrance)
Okay.
OK
(The order of entrance)
A hat and a mask, right?
有帽子和口罩OK
(A cafe in Jeju)
Let's do this.
真的來吧
My hair at the back of my head is too long.
我後面的頭髮太長了
(They even turned off the light.)
Kwang Soo, you look suspicious already.
光洙啊 你現在就很奇怪了
Should I put on a cap?
不戴圍巾嗎 戴帽子嗎
(They look suspicious even in darkness.)
You look suspicious.
你太奇怪了
People will recognize you as soon as you enter.
你一進去就結束了
(They're glad that the 1st player is Kwang Soo.)
Kwang Soo, it's game over.
光洙啊 你直接就結束了
- You should know that. - No.
你就這麼想吧
- I will show you. - Don't get your hopes up.
不是的 哥 我展示給你們看
不要期待
- Do you have a cap? - Where is it?
-有帽子嗎 -我的在哪裏
(The 1st team, Team Olympiad gets off.)
People rarely recognize me,
不太認得我 你感覺太明顯了
but you are too recognizable.
(Anyone will be able to tell that he is Lee Kwang Soo.)
I am wearing a school uniform too.
校服也是
(Even to me)
I am too tall to be a high schooler.
不是 高中生來說太高了
(Team Olympiad is already nervous.)
You are too tall to be a high schooler.
高中生來說太高了
We need to go that way. Isn't that the cafe?
在這邊
是不是這裏
(They act natural and approach the cafe.)
(However)
Why are there so many people?
呀人爲什麼這麼多啊
(Since it's 7:30pm on a weekday, the cafe is packed...)
(with students and office workers.)
(This footage was filmed safely and in accordance...)
Let's sit down first.
坐下 先坐下吧
(with COVID-19 prevention guidelines.)
(The two students enter.)
Let's sit down first.
坐下 先坐下吧
(The cafe is packed with customers.)
(A customer looks at Kwang Soo as soon as he enters.)
(Thankfully, he didn't recognize Kwang Soo.)
(A staff member's cell phone)
(They walk past the customers without ordering.)
(The direction Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo went)
Let's sit over there.
坐在那裏吧
(They arrive at a secluded place.)
(Whispering)
This table is perfect.
很好 這個位置剛剛好 不顯眼
No one will look at us.
(At that moment,)
(a customer looks at Ji Hyo!)
(She turns her head away.)
We look natural.
看起來特別自然
(Team Olympiad sneaked in pretty well.)
(Staring)
(More secluded)
I see more seats over there.
這裏還有呢
(What?)
(Is she looking at Kwang Soo?)
(Kwang Soo was looking for a more secluded spot...)
(when a female customer looked in his direction!)
If your name gets called, you are out.
先喊出名字的隊伍淘汰
(Did she recognize Kwang Soo?)
(Uninterested)
(She resumes talking to her friend.)
(Nervous)
Let's not move.
先不要動
(This high school student who is 2m tall can't even stand up.)
(While Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo overcome many crises,)
Let's not move.
先不要動
(Team Running Trading Company gets ready to enter.)
- What? - That's too obvious. I'm not lying.
什麼
講真哥像熊一樣
Really?
真的嗎
(Jong Kook and Haha can't cover themselves.)
Go.
走
- We need to cover the mic. - What?
麥克風要遮住纔行 哥
(They look like they're here to take over the cafe.)
Is it here?
這裏嗎
(A staff member's cell phone)
- Hello. - They're here.
- Jong Kook and Haha are here. - They're here?
進來了鍾國哥和HAHA哥進來了
進來了嗎
Hello.
(Humming)
(Jong Kook tries to act normal by humming.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(To be safe, they must grab a seat first.)
(A staff member's cell phone)
(Jong Kook sits down.)
(Haha moves to the other side.)
(They're going to split up to avoid suspicion.)
(Jong Kook, Haha)
(They safely grab a seat.)
- Haha. - Thank you. Bye.
(After 1 minute, Team Human Cultural Asset enters.)
- What? - Hey.
哥
Don't worry.
不用擔心
(Chuckling)
- Is it here? - Look at our pants.
這裏嗎
噗哈 但是我們褲子哈哈
(Flapping)
Our pants are...
褲子有點
(Two men enter flapping their pants.)
- Is it here? - I think so.
這裏嗎
- It's here. - Seriously.
安靜點
真的是
(A staff member's cell phone)
Hello.
(2 people in a weird hanbok appear in a cafe full of young people)
Welcome.
Your pants are embarrassing.
你的褲子更加
(Jae Seok is here.)
Jae Seok.
在錫哥
That's so weird.
不是那個太奇怪了吧
That's obviously Jae Seok.
任誰看都是在錫哥吧
He looks weird.
不是 穿戴太奇怪了吧
(They steal people's attention.)
- Welcome. - Your pants are embarrassing.
你的褲子更加
(As they walk, they can feel people looking at them.)
This is wrong.
不對不對
Let's go somewhere else.
呀去其他地方吧
(Embarrassed)
I didn't know it was this bright.
這個地方這麼明亮的嗎
(People in the cafe are stirred.)
- Hurry up. - Let's sit.
(They move in a rush.)
Why is it so bright?
Hurry up.
(What?)
(They enter a room.)
What are we doing?
(The human cultural asset and Seok Sam aren't used to a cafe.)
What's this place?
這是哪啊
- Why is it so bright? - What's this room?
怎麼這麼亮啊
I didn't expect it to be this bright.
這個位置
都被看到了
- What's this room? - What's this?
這是什麼位置啊
(They look suspicious even from behind.)
I think some people recognized us.
不過哥剛纔有沒有感覺好像有人認出來我們了
(A staff member's cell phone)
- What? - Some people recognized us.
是不是認出我們了啊
I think they recognized us.
好像認出來我們了
(People stare at them...)
I noticed my pants...
而且因爲這個褲子飄來飄去的
(because of their flapping pants.)
I saw you from the back.
我剛纔不是在你後邊走嗎
(No one has called their names yet.)
You look like a martial arts player.
感覺你就像個武道人一樣
我也是 真的太慌了
You should go place an order.
真的太慌張了
- I was so flustered. - People here don't know.
太慌了真的
不過這邊的人應該不知道
(Someone's approaching them.)
She's looking at Jae Seok.
有人往在錫哥那邊看了
(The customer grabs her phone...)
- Okay. - I think she's looking at us.
OK OK
(staring at Jae Seok and Seok Jin.)
好像是往我們這邊來了啊
(Glancing)
This is bad.
這下完了
(Please don't come.)
(Jong Kook's glancing at them.)
(She passes them.)
People here don't know yet.
這邊應該不知道
(Relieved)
Should I sit somewhere else?
我真是 應該坐在別的地方的嗎
I think some people noticed.
有幾位好像已經看出來了
They're here.
進來了 進來了
Who are they?
誰啊誰啊
(After 1 minute,)
Se Chan and So Min.
世燦和昭旻
Welcome.
(Team Newlyweds enters.)
They're here. They covered their faces perfectly.
昭旻進來了 他們遮得也太嚴實了
- Hello. - Hello.
-歡迎光臨 -歡迎光臨
-歡迎光臨 -這也太奇怪了吧
Don't they look weird?
(They look very suspicious.)
- They look suspicious. - They're wearing matching.
他們看起來太奇怪了啊
- They look so weird. - My goodness.
真的太奇怪了
(The newlywed couple doesn't look sweet at all.)
They're wearing matching clothes. That's so weird.
-他們和我們差不多啊 -太奇怪了啊
- They're wearing matching clothes. - What's up with them?
他們應該也能被認出來
他們是在幹嘛
Are they placing an order?
他們要點單嗎
Are they?
他們要點單了嗎
(A staff member's cell phone)
What are you having?
你要喝什麼
I'll sit over there.
我先去那邊坐着
(So Min's going to place an order to avoid suspicion.)
Well...
What would you like?
你要喝點什麼呢
(While So Min's ordering,)
Well...
哦 我要
(Se Chan sits in the corner.)
They're ordering something.
他們點東西了
Well...
那個
I'll have two iced tea.
我要兩杯冰茶
(The employee raises his head...)
I'll have two iced tea.
我要兩杯冰茶
(upon hearing So Min's voice.)
The part-timers and customers have no idea.
兼職生和客人們是完全不知道的
(Will he notice that it's So Min?)
(Very kind)
- Two iced tea? - Yes.
-兩杯冰茶是嗎 -是的
- For here? - Yes.
-是在店裏喝是嗎 -是的
(He focuses on his job with So Min in front of him.)
- Yes. - That's 5.8 dollars.
一共是5800韓元
I got so nervous that I ordered iced tea.
你知道嗎 我太緊張了所以就點了冰茶
(They successfully grab a seat with iced tea.)
- Good job. - Because I was so nervous.
因爲太緊張了
I was so nervous. I didn't know what to order.
實在不知道該點什麼了
- Let's go over there. Let's move. - Is there a table?
我們去那邊邊上坐着吧
(Team Human Cultural Asset aims at the partitioned area.)
- Is there a table? - Let's move over there.
-換個位置吧 -那邊有位置嗎
有位置嗎
Okay.
好像有位置 那邊最邊上
走吧
(They feel pressured since it's open.)
- Over there. - Let's go.
最邊上
(They quietly move to the partitioned area.)
(What? A glass wall?)
(Flustered)
There's a glass wall.
有玻璃牆
Why is there glass?
爲什麼有玻璃
(He almost broke a glass for trusting Seok Sam.)
There's glass.
我們怎麼
You said there's a door.
不是說有門嗎
(Because of two brothers who came to the dead end,)
It's glass.
門在那邊 我們得從那邊出去
(Jong Kook will be suspected.)
There's a table. We have to go now.
We have to go now.
現在得趕緊出去了
- We have to go. - Let's go.
得趕緊走了 走吧
(They try to move to the partitioned area again.)
(Running Man members think...)
Hello.
(they look natural if they put their hands in the pockets.)
(They all grabbed a seat.)
(Whispering)
You have to place an order.
該去點單了
(Since all 4 teams are here, Team 1 has to place an order first.)
We have to order.
該點單了嗎
He's ordering something.
去點東西了 去點東西了
Kwang Soo is too obvious.
光洙哥太明顯了吧
(2m-tall giant appeared in the cafe again.)
He's too obvious.
怎麼辦 光洙哥也太明顯了吧
Do I look weird?
姐
Look at me. Do I look weird?
看看我 我看起來不奇怪吧
Do we look weird?
你別做奇怪的事
Your order.
那姐你來點吧
Do you have money?
還可以嗎
Hello. What would you like?
客人您好 我來幫您點單
(Altering his voice)
- Peppermint... - Hot chocolate...
熱巧克力
(Despite altering his voice,)
- Peppermint... - Hot chocolate...
熱巧克力
(people focus on 2m-tall high school student.)
- Thank you. - Is it just one drink?
-謝謝光臨 -只點一杯飲料是嗎
We're going to share.
我們兩個要分着喝
Just one, please.
只要一杯就可以了
(When two students barely place an order,)
(one customer gets up and approaches them.)
(He approaches Kwang Soo.)
Excuse me.
請問
(He tries to talk to Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo.)
Excuse me.
請問
(If a customer says their names, they fail.)
Excuse me.
請問
Are you Lee Kwang Soo?
是李光洙嗎
(Careful)
Are you Lee Kwang Soo?
請問是李光洙嗎
(Pretending not to hear him)
Are you Song Ji Hyo?
是宋智孝對吧
(The producer appears.)
You failed the mission. Come back.
任務失敗了 請回去吧
(Team Olympiad fails the mission.)
(Oh, it's Lee Kwang Soo and Song Ji Hyo.)
(Laughing)
Kwang Soo got caught.
光洙哥被認出來了
Right. He got caught.
沒錯 被認出來了
(Despite various suspicious couples, Kwang Soo got caught.)
- They got caught. - Their mission is over.
怎麼辦 被認出來了
They got caught.
-結束了嗎 -被認出來了
(Hello.)
Hello.
(I'm your fan.)
- Kwang Soo got caught. - He got caught.
-光洙哥被認出來了 -被認出來了
My goodness.
怎麼辦
(Teasing)
Kwang Soo. Did you get caught?
哥 被認出來了吧
(2m-tall high school student is down after failing the mission.)
(V for victory)
Hey.
(Delinquent Ji Hyo appears.)
I told you not to open your eyes like that.
我說沒說過讓你別那樣了
(Letting Jong Kook know)
Lee Kwang Soo got caught.
李光洙被人認出來了
(The news about Kwang Soo's arrest is delivered to suspicious people.)
Is it over?
結束了嗎
- It's over. - Is it over?
-結束了結束了 -結束了嗎
(It's a surprise that they didn't get caught.)
- Did someone get caught? - Yes.
有人被認出來了嗎
Did Kwang Soo get caught?
李光洙被認出來了吧
(They cheer as the nervous mission ends.)
- He did. - I saw it.
李光洙被人認出來了
李光洙被認出來了
Who got caught?
誰被認出來了
Kwang Soo got caught.
李光洙被人認出來了
(Light steps)
- Okay, okay. - That's a relief.
-OK OK -真是
I was wrong to think...
我剛纔一直想錯了
(They survived from the edge of the cliff.)
- Where were you? - I didn't see you. Where were you?
哥在哪坐着呢
- I didn't see you. - But...
一直沒看到哥啊 哥在哪呢
-都沒看到哥 -不過
- We were in a room. - You don't know,
我們在房間裏坐着
(You know what?)
- but you all looked weird. - Really?
自己都不知道 但是大家都很奇怪
(All eight of them looked suspicious.)
- It's really suspicious. - You were really weird.
沒錯 真的是
你們也真的特別奇怪
When you walked in,
哥哥們進來的時候
I almost called the police.
我真的都想報警了
They looked so weird.
行爲舉止真的太異常了
We were surprised.
所以進去的時候我們也被驚到了
(Bright light and crowd were worst conditions.)
It was so bright.
太亮堂了
We were like, "My goodness."
而且走着走着就 抱歉
- And our pants were flapping. - That's funny.
-而且因爲這個褲子顯得更奇怪了 -太好笑了
(Thanks to the cafe and customers for cooperation.)
- We all looked weird. - We were all suspicious.
大家都太奇怪了
- Let's get in the car. - Get in the car.
真的都太奇怪了
先上車吧
It's worth calling the police.
-走吧 -剛纔真的特別
(Announcing the race result)
Here's the result of the last mission.
好了 最後一個任務的結果
(3 winners who will win a prize will be announced first.)
- I will announce three winners. - Who are they?
是
先發表最終獲勝的三個人
It's based on the number of stamps.
-是誰呢 -OK
這個是看圖章個數的
(Among 8 people, the person who collected the most stamps is...)
- Okay. - Oh, stamps.
好的
(1st place completed 4 courses.)
First place goes to...
第一名是
(It's Yu Jae Seok.)
Yu Jae Seok.
劉在錫
- Really? You placed first? - That's amazing.
-真的嗎 -真的嗎
(The human cultural asset participated in all courses.)
- Me? - Is it an individual play?
-哥是第一名嗎 -我嗎
這是個人戰嗎
- He played a lot. - Yes.
因爲哥出去的次數比較較多
(2nd place who will also receive a prize with 1st place is...)
Second place goes to...
然後第二名是
Jee Seok Jin, Kim Jong Kook and Yang Se Chan.
池石鎮 金鐘國 梁世燦
(Seok Jin, Se Chan, and Jong Kook placed 2nd.)
- Oh, really? - Me too?
我嗎
- That's awesome. - I didn't know.
-我都不知道 -好贊
We'll give these four people a prize.
所以我們將會爲這四位提供獎品
(All 4 people will receive a prize.)
So Min will purchase the prize tomorrow.
獎品將由全昭旻明天一起去購買
(So Min will buy the prize at the duty-free shop.)
- Am I buying them tomorrow? - Yes.
-明天我去買回來嗎 -是的
- Okay. - Goodness.
好的
(Announcing the penalty team)
Now, I have to announce the penalty.
接下來要發表懲罰
(While only one team is nervous, the penalty is revealed.)
Do we receive the penalty as a team?
懲罰是按隊接受的嗎
Yes.
是的
It's an opening penalty.
懲罰是 開場懲罰
(There will be an opening related penalty in a month.)
-OK -最近開場懲罰變得奇怪了
Lately, the opening penalty's getting weird.
(The opening penalty which they hate the most will be carried out.)
It's getting weird.
-特別麻煩 -特別折騰
- It's getting really weird. - It's very childish.
-特別麻煩的 -最不喜歡的
(They're complaining.)
- You have to come early. - You have to come early.
-得來得特別早 -要早點來
(It's ruined.)
- It's a hassle. - It's troublesome.
-而且比較麻煩的 -這個太麻煩了
- It's such a hassle. - It's troublesome.
特別麻煩
(Announcing the team money to determine the penalty)
Jae Seok and Seok Jin's Team Human Cultural Asset...
在錫石鎮 非物質文化遺產隊
has negative 655 dollars.
負65萬5千韓元
We spent a lot.
我們的有點多啊
Team Asst. Manager Ha and the New Recruit...
新人社員鍾國和HA代理
kept 10 dollars.
守住了原來的1萬韓元
(Team Running Trading Company didn't spend at all.)
Team Newlyweds has negative 314 dollars.
然後新婚夫妻是
-負31萬4千韓元 -OK
Next, Team Olympiad...
然後是奧林匹克競賽的優勝和準優勝是
has negative 1,212 dollars.
負121萬2千韓元
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo will receive a penalty.)
So they will have the opening penalty.
所以兩位當選開場懲罰
Come on
- Lee Kwang Soo. Seriously... - Come on.
Good good nice
-李光洙真是 -Come on
(The happy Jeju Island trip is over.)
That's the end of Part Two of Jeju Island Special.
濟州島特輯第二彈到這裏就結束了
Thank you.
-謝謝大家 -再見
(The next day)
(Duty free shop in Jungmun, Seogwipo)
This place is really big.
這裏真的好大啊
(Shopping completes the trip.)
I didn't know there was a duty free in south of Jeju Island.
濟州島南邊居然有這麼大的免稅店
(So Min chooses the prize for the winners.)
I should pick what best suits them.
我要挑一些合適的禮物
(Wine for Seok Jin who finally opened his eyes for alcohol)
I heard lately Seok Jin enjoys wine.
石鎮哥說自己最近喜歡喝紅酒
(Sweet snacks for Jae Seok who loves snacks)
This is perfect for Jae Seok.
這個送給在錫哥最合適了
Well...
I'll get cosmetics for Se Chan and Jong Kook.
世燦和鍾國哥送護膚品吧
(With gift shopping, Jeju Island Special ends.)
I'll make sure to deliver them to Seoul.
我會好好地送到首爾的
(It's fall, the season of delicacies.)
- Fall, the season for food... - It's food.
美食的季節 秋天
- Okay! - Nice.
-美食啊 -OK
(Old restaurant tour in Seoul)
- Old restaurants. - Old restaurants.
-Nice -歷史悠久的老店
(Famous food lover idols, Bo Mi and Nam Joo)
- Bo Mi! - It's Nam Joo.
-普美啊 -南珠啊
(People you want to eat with, Hoshi and Mingyu)
- They eat so much. - It's SEVENTEEN.
她們很能喫的
SEVENTEEN
(People you want to feed, Kim Soo Yong and Nam Chang Hee)
- Nam Chang Hee. - It's Soo Dragon!
-南昶熙 -秀-Dragon來啦
(Find the real old restaurant in Seoul with history.)
It shows their history.
能看出來是有歷史的
If Soo Yong and Seok Jin go, it's an old restaurant.
我們這邊
秀勇哥和石鎮哥進去的話就是老字號了
It's 200 years old.
年齡加一起都有200歲了
(No area...)
We have to go to Jongno.
得去鍾路那邊
(or menu...)
- 50 years in Myeongdong. - It's here.
-明洞50年老店 -就是這裏了
(is set.)
- I love Pyongyang naengmyeon. - How old is it?
平壤冷麪不錯
(They must cast the place themselves.)
Excuse me. How old is your restaurant?
這是多少年的
老闆 這家店開了多久了
When did you open the restaurant?
開店有多久了呢
(Hangover soup with 84 years of history)
We should go here.
得去這裏啊
We must try the gukbap with history.
得喫傳統的湯飯啊
It's 100 years old.
百年老店
(Ramyeon with 49 years of history)
This is 49-year-old ramyeon, So Min.
49年的店啊 昭旻啊
(The older the restaurant is, the younger they become.)
- It's younger than me? - Wait a minute.
-比我還小嗎 -等一下
(Journal of Old Restaurant)
- Awesome. - Let's go!
好贊
走起啊
(They fight to eat...)
(and to reduce their ages.)
- Hey! - Are you opening mine?
要我打開嗎
Stop it.
等一下啊
(What's the result of the old restaurant tour in Seoul?)